你要去哪裏 紫羅蘭？
Where you going, Violet?
摘幾朵花去
Just to pick some flowers.
不要走得太遠
Don't wander too far.
♪我狂野的愛爾蘭玫瑰♪
"My wild Irish rose"
♪最可愛的花長出來了♪
"The sweetest flower That grows"
♪你可以到處找♪
"You may search everywhere"
♪但沒有人能比得上♪
"But none can compare"
♪帶著我狂野的愛爾蘭玫瑰♪
"With my wild Irish rose "
好吧  你好
Well, hi there.
你在哪裏找到的
Where did you find those?
我知道所有的秘密地點
I know all the secret places.
你想要一個嗎？
Do you want one?
你想知道我為什麼戴著
You're wondering why I'm wearing
一頂有趣的帽子嗎
such a funny hat.
我總是戴著這頂帽子
I always wear this hat.
太多了 這是我名字的一部分
So much, it's a part of my name now.
我的朋友們...
My friends...
我最好的朋友 他們就叫我玫瑰帽
my very, very best friends, they just call me Rose the Hat.
看起來像魔術師的帽子
It looks like a magician's hat.
是的
It is.
這是一頂魔法帽子
It's a magic hat.
你想看看嗎？
Do you wanna see?
我袖子裏什麼都沒有
Nothing up my sleeves.
我的帽子裏什麼都沒有
Nothing in my hat.
別擔心  那是我的朋友
Don't worry, that's my friend.
你錯過了把戲
You're missing the trick.
把手伸進裏面
Reach inside.
哇！
Wow!
太漂亮了
It's so pretty.
因為它很特別
Because it's special.
說到特別
And speaking of special,
你也有點魔法 不是嗎？
you're a little magic, too, aren't you?
我手裏的花 是什麼顏色的？
The flower in my hand, what color is it?
哦 沒事的 親愛的
Oh, it's okay, honey.
你不會嚇到我的 我保證
You won't scare me. I promise.
紫色的
Purple.
紫羅蘭...
Violet...
就像你一樣
like you.
你不能吃花
You don't eat flowers.
但你能
But you do.
但這些很特別
But these are special.
親愛的 最好吃的是特別的
Honey, it's the special ones that taste best.
我應該回去找我媽媽了
I should get back to my mom.
不 留下來 呆一會兒 多看點魔術
No, stay. Stay awhile. See more magic.
噢
Ow.
你是個特別的小東西
You are a special little thing,
不是嗎？
aren't you?
紫羅蘭？
Violet?
紫羅蘭！
Violet!
紫...
Vi...
不要
Please.
嘿 沒關係的 道客
Hey. It's okay, Doc.
沒關係的
It's okay.
那兒
There.
全都干了
All dry.
出什麼事了？
What happened?
你得跟我說 丹尼
You have to talk to me, Danny.
我們離開後你就沒說過話...
You haven't talked since we left...
拜託 道客
Please, Doc.
拜託
Please.
那麼...
So...
你不說話 是吧 道客？
you ain't talking, huh, Doc?
我第一次見到你也沒怎麼說話
Weren't talking much first time I met you neither.
小男孩...
Little boy...
打算在那個破舊的地方度過一個漫長的冬天
set to spend a long winter at that rotten old place.
只有他和他的媽媽和爸爸
Just him and his mommy and daddy.
爸爸和那個男孩一樣黑
Daddy as dark as that boy is bright.
孩子 他很聰明
And, boy, is he bright.
他光芒四射...
He's shining like fire...
在那個地方...
in the one place...
對一個發光的人來說是最糟糕的地方
the worst place for someone who shines.
你還記得我們第一次真正交談嗎？
You remember the first time we really talked?
當我在你腦子裏說話的時候？
When I spoke up inside your head?
讓你感覺很好 對吧？
Made you feel good, right?
我知道你並不孤單
Knowing you weren't alone.
爸爸想殺了我
Daddy tried to kill me.
不全是他  你得知道
It wasn't all him, you gotta know.
那個地方給他帶來了黑暗  就像給你帶來光一樣
That place fed his dark, like it fed on your light.
他身上也有光
And he had some light in him, too.
就像你有黑暗一樣
Just like you got some dark.
我們兩個都有
We all got both.
我還沒完呢
It's not done with me.
你有沒有想過我是怎麼出現的？
It ever strike you funny how I showed up when I did?
當你需要我的時候
When you needed me.
有人也為我這麼做了
Someone did that for me, too.
我奶奶教我的
My grandma taught me,
我教過你
and I taught you.
總有一天 丹尼·托倫斯 你會教別人的
And some day, Danny Torrance, you'll teach someone else.
我不會的
I won't.
哦 你不會的 嗯？
Oh, you won't, huh?
我不會發光的 我是說
I won't shine, I mean.
不會了 很危險
No more. It's dangerous.
有時候也是這樣
Reckon it is sometimes.
她找到我了
She found me.
她會回來的  直到她得到我
She'll come back and come back until she gets me.
你說得對
You're right.
俯瞰者被判有罪  封住他
The Overlook's condemned. Boarded up.
他們是飢餓的老鬼
They're starvin' old ghosts,
他們在找你
and they're reachin' out for you.
她也不會罷休的
Won't stop with her, either.
書裏的照片
Pictures in a book.
你說它們只是一本書裏的照片  它們傷害不了我
You said they were just pictures in a book and they couldn't hurt me.
一些事情
Some things,
黑暗的東西  閃閃發光就像食物
dark things, the shining's like food.
它們是蚊子在吸血
They're mosquitoes landing for blood.
《俯瞰》
The Overlook,
對我來說只是照片
it was always just pictures to me.
但我不像你那樣光彩照人
But I didn't shine like you.
沒人像你一樣
Nobody shines like you.
所以 你在那該死的酒店裏 就像一個百萬瓦的電池
So, you in that damn hotel, you was like a million-watt battery
全部插上電源
all plugged in.
它把它吃光了
And it ate it up.
你做到了
You made it real.
你一進門就開始了
Started soon as you walked through the door.
對此我無能為力 很抱歉告訴你
Can't do nothing about that, I'm sorry to tell you,
但你不是孩子
but you're not a child.
你現在老了
You're older now.
在某種程度上 要老得多
Much older, in a way.
你得聽聽這個
You gotta hear this.
世界是個飢餓的地方
World's a hungry place.
最黑暗的東西是最飢餓的  他們會吃掉發光的東西
And the darkest things are the hungriest, and they'll eat what shines.
像蚊子或水蛭一樣成群結隊的
Swarm it like mosquitoes or leeches.
對此我無能為力
Can't do nothing about that.
你所能做的...
What you can do...
就是讓他們反對他們
is turn what they come for against 'em.
我祖父
My grandfather,
他是個刻薄的狗娘養的
he was a mean son of a bitch.
內心黑暗
Dark inside.
和你爸爸一樣的黑暗
Same type of dark as your dad.
把我打昏  我奶奶也被打
Beat me senseless, and my grandma, too,
當他死的時候  我高興的跳舞
and when he died, I danced.
但他總是回來
But he kept on coming back.
站在我的房間裏
Standing in my room.
煙熏得又黑又臭
Suit all gray and stinkin'
不管他在那個盒子里長了什麼黴菌
from whatever mold was growin' on him in that box.
有一天 他抓住了我 他是真實的
One day, he grabbed me, and he was real.
他的指甲很長
His nails were long
從墳墓裏生長出來
from growing in the grave,
他們割傷了我  道格
and they cut me, Doc.
割傷我
Cut me deep.
所以 奶奶
So, Grandma,
她教了我一個把戲
she taught me a trick.
給了我一份禮物
Gave me a present.
我想讓你知道這個盒子...
I want you to know this box...
從裏到外
inside and out.
不要只看它 摸摸它
Don't just look at it. Touch it.
把你的鼻子插進去 看看有沒有味道
Stick your nose inside and see if there's a smell.
瞭解每一個角落
Know every corner,
每個特點
every single thing.
為什麼？
Why?
因為你要在腦海裏建立一個和它一樣的盒子
Because you're gonna build one just like it in your mind.
一個更特別的
One even more special.
所以下次那個婊子來的時候
So next time that bitch comes around,
你會準備好的
you'll be ready.
我們帶你回去找媽媽
Let's get you back to Mama.
溫迪會擔心的
Wendy'll worry,
她不應該再為她的生活擔心了
and she shouldn't have to worry another day in her life.
那女人已經還清了債
That woman's paid her debt.
丹尼！
Danny!
你在這兒
There you are.
你去哪了 嗯？
Where did you go, huh?
你把我嚇得半死
You scared me half to death.
別這樣對我 你聽見了嗎？
Don't you do that to me. You hear?
你別這樣對我
Don't you ever do that to me.
別這樣對我
Don't ever do that to me.
怎麼了 醫生？
Eh, what's up, Doc?
你說什麼？
What's the bit?
什麼是烹飪？
What's cookin'?
你在做什麼 小朋友？為什麼 你是
What's cooking, little friend? Why, you are.
我？
Me?
為什麼 是的
Why, yes.
哎喲！你要殺了我！
Ouch! You're killing me!
哎喲！
Ouch!
痛苦！痛苦！
Agony! Agony!
讓我看看
Let me see now.
很顯然 這不是普通的兔子
It is obvious that this is no ordinary rabbit.
因此 我必須想出一個聰明的策略 巧妙的...
Therefore, I must dream up a brilliant master strategy, ingenious...
你還好吧 道格？
You okay, Doc?
如果我引誘他...
Now, uh, what if I lured him...
-是的 媽媽我沒事  -...進入岩石破碎機？
- Yeah, Mom. I'm okay. - ...into a rock crusher?
不 不 太複雜了
Nah, nah, nah, too complicated.
對 對 太複雜了 但如果我...
Yeah, yeah, too complicated. But what if I...
呃 太多細節了
Uh-uh, too much detail.
好吧 太多細節了
Right. Too much detail.
你叫什麼名字 甜心？
And what's your name again, cutie?
丹
Dan.
我在和那位女士喝一杯 好嗎？
I was having a drink with the lady, all right?
嘿 你要吃藥了
Hey. You're gonna take your medicine.
離他遠點
Get off him.
站起來 離開這裏
Get up. Get out of here.
他媽的 我想是你殺了他
Shit. I think you killed him.
如果你殺了他呢？
What if you killed him?
希望你殺了他
I hope you killed him.
你聽到了嗎？
You hear me?
讓我吻它
Let me kiss it better.
不
No.
不  不  不
No, no, No.
不
No
哇哦 什麼......不
Whoa. What the... No.
你叫什麼名字 英雄？
What's your name, hero?
-媽媽？-寶貝
- Mommy? - Baby.
這裏 這裏
Here, here.
你可以把她的錢放回去  道格
You can put her money back, Doc.
你可以做很多
You can do that much.
她拿走了我的
She took mine.
她可能用它買了可樂
She probably bought the coke with it.
道格
Doc.
不 不 Doc
No, no, Doc.
你可以把東西放在盒子裏
You can put things from the Overlook away in boxes,
但不是回憶
but not memories.
不是那些
Never those.
他們才是真正的鬼魂
They're the real ghosts.
你帶著他們
You take them with you.
該睡覺了 阿布拉
Time for bed, Abra.
再來一點
A little more.
不行  親愛的
No more, sweetie.
明天是個大日子
Big day tomorrow.
-生日聚會！-沒錯
- Birthday party! - That's right.
是的
Yeah.
現在幾點了？
Now, what time is it?
-就寢時間 -你知道現在是睡覺時間
- Bedtime. - You know it's bedtime.
晚安 甜心
Good night, sweetheart.
♪還是以前的故事♪
"It's still The same old story"
♪為愛和榮耀而戰♪
"A fight for love and glory"
♪世界將永遠歡迎愛♪
"The world will always Welcome lovers"
♪隨著時間的流逝♪
"As time goes by"
亨利要我們喝完這個瓶子  然後再來三瓶
Henri wants us to finish this bottle and then three more.
安迪？
Andi?
他說他會用香檳給花園澆水...
Says he'll water his garden with champagne...
是的
That's right.
。 在他讓德國人喝之前
...before he'll let the Germans drink it.
這種方法可以使被佔領的人擺脫痛苦.
This sort of takes the sting out of being occupied.
你比照片漂亮
You're prettier than your picture.
-不是嗎 理查德先生？-你說的
- Doesn't it, Mr. Richard?  -You said it.
而且你比你說的年齡大
And you're older than yours.
我們是呆在這裏還是去別的地方？
Are we staying here or going somewhere?
你不想看電影嗎？
Don't you wanna watch the movie?
我看不出有什麼大驚小怪的
I don't see what the fuss is about.
聊天室的浪漫
Chat room romance.
有點噁心  一點都不有趣
Little gross. Not interesting.
你看著點  很有趣  我保證
Just watch. It's interesting, I promise.
最好是這樣  因為她不是那麼潮
Well, it better be, 'cause she's not all that steamy.
她來了
And there she goes.
你不累嗎？
Aren't you tired?
睡吧
Sleep.
好吧
Okay.
等等 這是最好的部分
Wait. This is the best part.
我看著她做了三次 而且永遠不會變老
I watched her do it three times now and it never gets old.
睡得更深入點
Sleep deeper,
盡你所能的深入
deep as you can.
你感覺到的痛苦只是一個夢
The pain you feel is only a dream.
會有什麼痛苦？
What will the pain be?
一個夢
A dream.
你可以解釋丟失的錢包
You can explain a lost wallet
當你妻子問的時候
when your wife asks.
但你不能解釋
But you can't explain this.
當你照鏡子的時候 你每天都會看到這個
This you'll see every day when you look in the mirror.
每次你看到它
And every time you see it,
你要大聲說出來...
you'll say out loud...
「我喜歡小女孩」
"I like little girls."
你會大聲說出來的
You'll say it out loud.
大聲說出來
Out loud.
下次你去網上找個小女孩的時候
And the next time you go looking for a little girl online,
我要你記住那段時間
I want you to remember that time
你被蛇咬了
you got bit by a snake.
被穿白色上衣的蛇咬了
A snake in a white blouse
他的臉是空白的
whose face is a blank.
-這很有趣  -嗯
- That is interesting. - Mm-hmm.
不好意思  小姐？
Excuse me, miss?
小姐 小姐 你在劇院留下了什麼東西
Miss. Miss, you left something in the theater.
你想離我遠點
You wanna leave me alone.
嘿  你好
Well, hi there.
你想放我走
You wanna let me go.
哦  不  親愛的
Oh, no, sweetie.
不 我不會
No, I don't.
我能走多遠？
How far can I get for this?
四個黑桃  這是什麼顏色的？
Four of spades. What color is this?
媽媽 這是我為你做的 這是一張秘密卡片
Mommy, I made this for you. It's a secret card.
嗯 謝謝你 阿巴杜
Mm, thank you, Abba-doo.
有人知道一個神奇的詞嗎？
Does anyone know a magic word?
-哦 哦 -呃...你
- Ooh, ooh. - Uh... You.
阿布拉卡達布拉拉
Abracadabra
阿布拉卡達布拉 太棒了
Abracadabra. That's a great one.
好吧 你拿著魔杖
Okay, you hold the magic wand.
現在 各位
Now, everyone,
數到三 好嗎？
on the count of three, okay?
-一 二 三
- One, two, three.
阿布拉卡達布拉拉
Abracadabra
我也懂魔法
I know magic, too.
好吧 那你就抱著他 生日女孩
Well, then you get to hold him, birthday girl.
-給你   你抓到他了？ -哦
- There you go. You got him? - Oh.
為了我的下一個把戲...哦 我的天 對不起
For my next trick... Oh, my goodness. Sorry.
有時候 如果我...
Sometimes, if I...
不好意思
Sorry.
有人看到我的勺子了嗎？
Has anyone seen my spoons?
我能做到
I can do that.
很好 親愛的
That's nice, sweetie.
-他們在你身上！-哦 他們在我身上？
- They're on you! - Oh, they're on me?
好吧 確保你們不要這麼做
Okay, make sure you guys don't do this.
哦！
Oh!
呃...我們可以忘了午睡時間
Uh... We can forget about naptime.
-再過幾個小時 -嗯
- Just a few more hours. - Mm.
跟我說吧 「再過幾個小時 」
Say it with me. "Just a few more hours."
再過幾個小時
Just a few more hours.
怎麼回事？
What the hell?
戴夫...
Dave...
阿布拉卡達布拉拉
Abracadabra
哎呀
Oops.
嗨 你好啊 瞌睡蟲
Well, hi there, sleepyhead.
打擾了
Sorry.
我不得不讓你睡得很沉
I had to sleep you pretty hard.
你是個堅強的人
You're a tough one.
任性
Willful.
你知道  我查過了
You know, I checked.
三個月六個男人
Six men in three months
臉頰上有那些小蛇咬傷的紋身
with those little snakebite tattoos on their cheeks.
為什麼  你一直很忙
Why, you've been busy.
蛇咬安迪  那就是你
Snakebite Andi, that's who you are.
那麼  我是誰？
So, who am I?
你就是個綁架我的瘋女人
You're some crazy bitch who kidnapped me.
從現在起只是真相
Just the truth from now on.
你只會說實話
You will only speak the truth.
你是我見過的最漂亮的女人
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
上帝啊  效果有點太好了  不是嗎？
My God. Works a little too well, don't it?
這就是交易  蛇咬安迪
Here's the deal, Snakebite Andi.
你是個推手 嗯？你可以催眠人
You're a pusher, hmm? You can push people.
我們已經有一段時間  沒人在這兒幫忙了
We haven't had a pusher around here for a little while,
所以我要給你一個我近40年都沒給過的交易
so I'm gonna offer you a deal I haven't offered anyone in almost 40 years.
你多大了 達林？
How old are you, darlin'?
15歲
Fifteen.
15歲？
Fifteen?
哦 天哪 多大的年紀啊
Oh, God, what an age.
女人的春天 不是嗎？
Springtime of your womanhood, isn't it?
嗯 你不再是個女孩了
Mm. You're not a girl anymore,
但你也沒有一個凹痕
but you don't have a single dent yet either.
萬有引力根本沒注意到你
Gravity hasn't even noticed you.
不是15歲
Not at 15.
但是  男人...
Men, though...
不  不  不害羞
No, no, no. No shame.
你還回來了  是不是？
You paid that back, didn't you?
這就是我給你的 一直到春天
That's what I'm offering you. Springtime forever.
十年後 你還是15歲
Ten years from now, you're still 15.
一百 也許十七
A hundred, maybe 17.
吃得好
Eat well,
保持年輕 長壽
stay young, live long.
你和你的朋友...
So, you and your friend...
嗯 不是我朋友 那是我的家人
Mm, not my friend. That's my family.
我們是真正的結 親愛的
We're the True Knot, dear.
真正的結
The True Knot.
交織在一起的東西永遠不能解開
What's tied can never be untied.
你喜歡嗎？
You like it?
哦 對不起 我只是...
Oh. Sorry. I was just...
沒關係的 人們喜歡看它
That's okay. People love to look at it.
我們以前在圖書館裏設置過這個
We used to set this up in the library.
社區項目  只不過是自謀生路而已
Community project, just taking a life all its own.
看  我們從那裏的鐘樓開始
See, we started with the clock tower There.
-哦 是的   -隻是不斷成長
- Oh, yeah. - Just keeps growing.
孩子們叫它蒂尼敦
Kids call it Teenytown.
孩子們造這個？
The kids build this?
在一些幫助下  是的
With some help, oh, Yeah.
堅持下去  建設全鎮廣場..
Keep it up, build the whole town square.
你是下車還是騎著大拇指？
Are you off the bus or riding your thumb?
是的 公共汽車
Yeah, the bus.
哦 很少有人坐公共汽車到這麼遠的北方
Oh. Not many ride the bus this far north.
除非他們在找工作
Unless they're looking for work.
是的
Yeah.
換個地方
Change of scenery,
還是你逃避什麼？
or you running away from something?
哦 別介意我 希望我是...
Oh, don't mind me. I hope I'm...
新面孔就是全部
New face is all.
是的
Yeah.
我想我是在逃避我自己吧
Guess I'm running away from myself, I guess.
是的
Oh, Yeah.
我知道那種表情 太好了 我很抱歉地說
I know that look. Too well, I'm sorry to say.
離開你自己 那真是個難題
Running away from yourself. That is a pickle.
無論你走到哪裏 你都要帶著自己
You take yourself with you wherever you go.
-那不是婊子嗎？-嗯
- Ain't that the bitch? - Mm-hmm.
房租是每周85英鎊
Rent's 85 a week,
先付
payable up front.
比利替你付了頭兩筆錢  剩下的就靠你了
Billy paid your first two, rest's on you.
不許養寵物  不許聚會  不許有噪音
No pets, no parties, no noise.
我是一個安靜的中尉
I'm a quiet tenant.
最後一個人也這麼說  數學生
Last guy said the same. Math student.
即使讓他把牆漆成黑板
Even let him paint the wall all blackboard,
這樣他就可以在上面塗鴉他的小拼圖了
so he could scribble his little puzzles up There.
不安靜   不  先生
Wasn't quiet. No, sir.
他離開的時候連畫都沒畫 但我很高興他沒有畫
Didn't even paint over this when he left, but I'm glad he didn't,
因為我可以讓你輕鬆點
'cause I can make this easy for ya,
所以你每天早上醒來都會看到它
so you see it every morning when you wake.
你真的想為這隻小狗擔保嗎？
You sure you wanna vouch for this pup?
很確定
Pretty sure.
是你的錯  比利
It's your ass, Billy.
心臟在滴血  這次
Bleedin' heart, this one.
我在樓下 一樓 如果你需要什麼
I'm downstairs, ground floor, if you need anything.
明天找我 談談工作
Find me tomorrow, talk about some work.
你為什麼這麼做？
Why are you doing this?
你不瞭解我
You don't know me.
是的  我不知道
No, I don't.
但我知道你的表情 就像我說的
But I know the look, like I said.
有時候我會對人產生這種感覺
And sometimes I get this feeling about people.
-我想很難理解   -嗯
- Hard to understand, I guess. - Mm.
比你想像的容易
Easier than you think.
-謝謝 -好吧
- Thanks. - All right.
準備好了嗎？
You ready?
她準備好了
She's ready.
誰...這些人是誰？
Who... Who are these people?
你會發現的
You'll find out after.
那邊是格拉姆帕·弗利克...
That over there is Grampa Flick...
他會帶領我們 躺下
and he'll lead us. Lie down.
這裏
There.
不用害怕 你明白嗎？
No fear. You understand?
我們是真正的結
We are the True Knot
我們要忍耐
and we endure.
我們是被選中的人
We are the chosen ones.
我們是幸運的人
We are the fortunate ones.
交織在一起的東西不能解開
What is tied cannot be untied.
這是一個女人
Here is a woman.
她會加入我們嗎？
Would she join us?
她會把她的生活和我們的生活聯繫起來嗎？
Would she tie her life to our life?
是的
Yes.
說  是的
say,Yes.
這個很特別
This one's special.
她叫維奧萊特
Her name's Violet.
她剩下的不多了
There's not much of her left.
她嘗起來...
And she tastes...
...就像花
...like flowers.
深呼吸
Breathe deep.
在那兒 擁抱它
There. Embrace it.
擁抱它
Embrace it.
不！
No!
他們還沒找到我們
They haven't found us yet.
他們習慣於聽到他的哭聲
They were used to hearing him cry
因為我讓他一個人呆著
'cause I left him alone so much.
所以他們什麼也沒做
So they didn't do anything.
他們還沒找到我們
And They haven't found us yet.
媽媽？
Mommy?
哦  嘿
Oh, hey.
你說你知道我的長相
Uh, you said that you knew my look.
你什麼意思？
Well, what did you mean?
兄弟...
Brother...
你病了
you're sick.
你累了  我能看到那麼多
You're tired. I can see that much.
但你厭倦了生病和疲勞
But you're sick and tired of being sick and tired.
我需要幫助
I need help.
快進來
Come on in.
我們談談
We'll talk about it.
上帝 賜予我平靜去接受我無法改變的事情
God, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change,
有勇氣去改變我能做的事
the courage to change the things I can,
知道不同的智慧
and the wisdom to know the difference.
巴比今天過了個大生日
Well, Bobbie's got a big birthday today.
三年  三年清醒
Three years. Three years sober.
是的
Yeah.
我真為你驕傲
I'm so proud of you.
謝謝 約翰
Thanks, John.
我是不是忘了什麼人？
Now, am I forgetting anybody?
有人有一年嗎？或者六個月？
Does anybody got a year? Or six months?
好吧 現在是房間裏最重要的人
Well, now for the most important person in the room.
有人是新來的嗎？
Is, uh, anybody here a newbie?
有人有24小時嗎？
Somebody got 24 hours?
是的
Yeah.
新來的 嗯？
New to town, huh?
是啊 我 呃...
Yeah, I, uh...
不是針對個人的 我在房間裏送了一半的人
Nothing personal. I delivered half the people in the room.
-隻是新面孔流行 僅此而已 -我是丹·托倫斯
- Just new faces pop, that's all. - This here is Dan Torrance.
-他剛下公共汽車  -嘿
- He's fresh off the bus. - Hey.
看起來  很新鮮的泥土
Fresh off the ground, by the look.
哦
Oh.
這裏沒有評判 兄弟
There's no judgment here, brother.
我是說  我們都去過那裏
I mean, we've all been There.
-更糟的是  相信我 -哦  是的
- And worse, trust me. - Oh, Yeah.
醫生 他為我們鎮服務了大半輩子
Doc, he's served our town most my life.
把我弟弟送來了
Delivered my baby brother.
是的 弗蘭基最近怎麼樣？
Yeah. How is Frankie these days?
他會找到回來的路的
Well, he'll find his way back.
你知道 他有一顆善良的心
You know, he's got a good heart under it all.
比利真的試過了 嗯 我們都做到了
Billy really tried with him. Well, we all did.
比利 你知道 如果你想找一隻翅膀爬到下面...
Well, Billy, you know, if you're looking for a wing to climb under...
...我不能說你會做得更好
...I can't say you'll do any better
比比利·弗裏曼這裏
than Billy Freeman here.
謝謝你的款待 我...
Thank you for your hospitality. I...
我有點 呃...
I'm a little, uh...
我想我不習慣
I guess I'm not used to it.
嗯  你知道嗎  我們會說
Well, you know we say,
「除非你知道某人的全部情況 否則你不能評判他 」
"You can't judge someone till you know their whole story."
你可能認為你明白
You might think you understand,
-但你沒有  -你不知道
- but you don't. - You don't.
你今天怎麼樣？好嗎？
So, how are you today? All right?
列車還在運行
Train's still running.
很高興聽到
That's good to hear.
你還好嗎？
You good?
是的
Yeah. Yeah.
很高興認識你 丹
Well, good to know you, Dan.
-是的 -再來一次
- Yeah. - Come again.
-謝謝 -希望不久能再見到你
- Thanks. - Hope to see you again soon.
我會     我會再來的  是的
I'll... I'll come back, Yeah.
很好的人 他有天賦...
Really good man. He's got a gift...
是的 嘿 比利 等等
Yeah. Hey, Billy, hang on.
嘿 醫生
Hey, Doc.
你的手錶 呃...
Your watch. Uh...
你的手錶丟了 你很擔心那個孩子...
You lost your watch. You were worried about the kid with, uh...
戈徹
Goocher's.
什麼？
What?
有個戈徹或高徹的孩子  關於骨頭的事
The kid with Goocher's or Gaucher's. The bone thing.
高徹氏病
Gaucher's disease.
好吧
Right.
你在醫院的浴室裏洗手
You were washing your hands in the hospital bathroom
你把手錶忘在肥皂分配器上了
and you left it on the soap dispenser.
好吧 看看肥皂分配器
Well, just check on the soap dispenser.
-很高興認識你   -好
- It's good to meet you. - Yeah.
你怎麼知道的？
How did you know?
我希望我能說 呃...
I wish I could say. Uh...
很幸運的猜測
Lucky guess.
胡說
My ass.
我想是直覺吧 就像我內心的一種感覺 可能是...
Intuition, I suppose. Like a feeling in my gut. Maybe a...
很幸運的猜測
A Lucky guess.
你想在這裏做什麼？
What do you wanna do here?
你什麼意思？
What do you mean?
我是說在弗雷澤 你為什麼在這裏？
I mean here in Frazier. Why are you here?
不要和我胡扯  丹
And don't bullshit me, Dan.
我喜歡自己的直覺
I'm prone to gut feelings of my own.
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
一些和我所做的不同的事情
Something different than I've been doing.
更好的事情
Something better.
坦白說  一切都好
Anything's better, frankly.
你去教堂？
You go to church?
有關係嗎？
Does it matter?
你相信什麼嗎？一些事情...
Do you believe in something? Something...
比你重大？
bigger than you?
我們的...我們的信仰不能讓我們變得更好
Our... Our beliefs don't make us better people.
我們的行動讓我們變得更好
Our actions make us better people.
所以 比利說你具有條理的能力
So, Billy says you have orderly experience.
是的
That's right.
你現在在工作嗎？
You workin' right now?
在蒂尼鎮的幾個班次  幫著坐火車
A few shifts at Teenytown. Helping with the train.
因為我每周在瑞溫頓收容所住三天
'Cause I do three days a week at Rivington House, the hospice.
好的秩序很難找到
Good orderly is tough to find.
更難保持
Tougher to keep.
垂死的人會打擾你嗎？
Do dying people bother you?
沒有
No.
我們都快死了
We're all dying.
世界是一個有著新鮮空氣的大型收容所
The world is one big hospice with fresh air.
嗯
Hmm.
噢
WOw.
嘿  你好
Well, hi there.
我這樣多長時間了    -哦  幾天了
- How long was I... - Oh, few days.
你說過不疼的
You said it didn't hurt.
現在不疼了  不是嗎？
Doesn't now, does it?
-感覺我快要死了   -嗯
- Felt like I was dying. - Mm.
我知道
I know.
你做到了
You did.
你帶我回來了
You brought me back.
吃點東西  你會感覺更好
You'll feel better when you eat.
我還是人類嗎？
Am I still human?
你在乎嗎？
Do you care?
♪現在都忘了♪
"It's all forgotten now"
♪麻煩和痛苦♪
"The trouble and the pain"
♪忘記了 我說的每一句話♪
"Forgotten, Every word I said"
♪忘記了 你流下的每一滴眼淚♪
"Forgotten, Every tear you shed"
♪我們還相愛♪
"We're still in love"
給你
There you go.
是什麼？
What is it?
你害怕我
You're scared of me.
哦...
Oh...
我們愛你勝過世界上任何東西
We love you more than anything in the world.
你聽到了嗎？
You hear me?
任何東西
Anything.
晚安  我的甜心
Goodnight, my heart.
嘿  讓他來吧
Hey. Let him be.
阿茲雷爾  別管他了
Azreel, leave him be.
伊茲？
Azzie?
伊茲 別這樣
Azzie, come on.
快點 伊茲
Come on. Azzie.
醫生
Doc.
是你嗎 醫生？
That you, Doc?
不 我不是醫生
No, I'm not a doctor.
你想讓我給你找個醫生嗎？
Do you want me to get you a doctor?
貓在我床上
The cat's on my bed.
噢 嘿 我會把她搬走的
Oh, hey, I'll move her.
不
No.
我知道她會的
I knew she would be.
那隻貓似乎總是知道...
That cat always seems to know...
當時間結束的時候
when it's time.
-我想是時候了  -沒有
- I guess it's time. - No.
阿茲只是一隻傻乎乎的老貓
It's just Azzie being a silly old cat.
不是
Nope.
從我到這裏起就是這樣
Been that way ever since I got here.
貓知道
The cat knows
是時候睡覺了
when it's time to go to Sleep.
所有人都知道
Everybody knows that.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
是的
Yes.
我去叫人
Let me get you someone.
別
No.
知道它要來了
Known it was comin'.
不會讓它變的不那麼可怕
Doesn't make it less scary.
是的
Yeah.
但也許就像你說的
But maybe it's just like you say,
只是去睡一覺
just going to Sleep.
我是說 沒什麼可怕的 只是在睡覺
I mean, there's nothing scary. It's just sleeping.
你是個奇怪的醫生
You're a strange type of doctor.
我告訴過你 我不是醫生
I told you, I'm not a doctor.
噢 我想是的
Oh, I think you are.
醫生   睡吧
Doctor Sleep.
醫生 我很害怕會受傷 或者遁入黑暗
Doc, I am so scared it's gonna hurt, or be dark,
或者...或者什麼都不是 我不想...
or... or be nothing at all. And I don't wanna...
沒什麼好怕的
Nothing to be scared of.
只是睡著了
Just going to sleep.
最終的  真正的  寧靜的睡眠
Finally, true, restful sleep.
哦 謝謝
Oh, thank you.
謝謝你  醫生
Thank you, Doc.
聽著 我不該在這裏 我去給你拿點...
Look, I shouldn't be here. Let me go get you some...
不  不  不
No, no, No.
你在你該在的地方
You're exactly where you should be.
應該
Exactly.
我看到我妻子了
I see my wife.
丹  酒鬼
Dan, alcoholic.
嘿  丹
Hi, Dan.
我不太喜歡演講
I'm not much of a speech guy.
我只是想拿著芯片  隨便說點什麼
I just thought I'd hold the chip and talk about whatever popped up.
所以  我來了
So, here I am.
我在想我爸爸
And I'm thinkin' about my dad.
我在他手裏看到過這樣的籌碼
I saw a chip like this in his hand once.
在他死前幾個月
A couple months before he died.
五個月的籌碼  我很確定
Five month chip, I'm Pretty sure.
他喝醉的時候傷害過我一次
He hurt me once when he was drunk.
弄斷了我的胳膊
Broke my arm.
然後他就一口氣喝完了
Then he dried right out.
他在我五歲的時候就死了  所以我想瞭解他的方式
He died when I was five, so the only way I got to know him,
真正瞭解他的唯一方式  就是在天黑的時候
really got to know him, was when I went dark.
當我...當我喝醉的時候...
When I... When I drank to dull the...
或者 呃...
or, uh...
每當我想打破別人的臉
whenever I wanted to break someone's face,
因為喝酒  發脾氣  發怒
'cause the drinking and the temper and the anger,
我身上的這些毛病 也是是他具有的
those things in me were his.
通過這些毛病我能瞭解到 關於他的一切
And they were all I could know of him.
但現在 好吧 現在我認識的他有點不同了...
But now, well, now I get to know him a little different...
因為他也曾站在這樣的房間裏...
'cause he also stood in a room like this once...
想讓我和我媽媽好起來
wanting to get well for me and my mom.
他手裏拿著籌碼
And he held the chip in his hand
籌碼說五個月
and the chip said five months,
在那天 他...
and on that day, he...
在這之前...
Before it all...
好吧 那天 他想要的一切
Well, on that day, all he wanted in the world
就是站在我站的地方
was to stand where I'm standing now.
我在這裏
And here I am,
所以謝謝你們二位  我想
so thank you for us both, I guess.
這是給傑克·托倫斯的
This is for Jack Torrance.
嘿  查理
Hey, Charlie.
醫生？
Doc?
我想我不需要問你為什麼在這個時候來這裏
Guess I don't need to ask why you're here at this hour.
你有疼痛嗎？
Do you have pain?
你想讓我讓克勞德特給你帶藥嗎？
Do you want me to get Claudette to bring you a pill?
吃藥不重要
Pill won't matter.
我聽到了家裏的電話
I heard about these house calls.
《睡眠博士》真是一部多麼好的電影啊！
What a visit from Doctor Sleep really is.
你看到什麼了 醫生？
So, what do you see, Doc?
我看到你的雙胞胎兒子了
I see your twin sons.
四歲
Four years old.
你能看到他們嗎？
Can you see them?
我能
I do.
農場拖拉機
Farmall tractor.
座位上有一把條紋的傘
A striped umbrella over the seat.
五歲
Five years old,
拉著一輛紅色的貨車
pulling a red wagon.
上帝啊  看看這個
Lord, look at that.
就像一副牌
Like a deck of cards.
一切都不正常
All out of order.
我不怕地獄  醫生
I'm not scared of hell, Doc.
我過著體面的生活
Uh, I lived a decent life.
反正我不認為有這樣的地方
I don't think there is such a place anyway.
我想我不害怕...
I guess I'm scared...
沒什麼可害怕的
there's Nothing.
以前也沒有
There was nothing before.
那麼 如果之後那邊也沒什麼可害怕的
So, what if there's nothing after?
我們不會結束的  查理
We don't end, Charlie.
我當然知道
I know that for certain.
我不知道還有什麼...
I don't know much else...
但我知道我們不會結束
but I know that we don't end.
藍莓
Blueberries.
我能嘗到我媽媽以前常吃的藍莓
I can taste blueberries my mother used to grow.
你能嘗嘗嗎？
Can you taste them?
-是的  我可以  -啊
- Yeah, I can. - Ah.
我能從你的收音機裏聽到弗蘭克的聲音
And I can hear Frank on your old radio.
你以前在工作台上的那個
The one you used to have on your workbench
在你的工具旁邊
next to your tools.
♪跟我一起飛吧♪
"Come fly with me"
？我們飛吧 飛走吧？
"Let's fly, let's fly away"
♪如果你能喝一些異國情調的酒♪
"If you can use Some exotic booze"
♪在遙遠的孟買有家酒吧♪
"There's a bar in far Bombay"
♪跟我一起飛吧♪
"Come fly with me"
♪我們飛 我們飛...♪
"Let's fly, let's fly..."
♪走吧♪
"Away"
只是一分鐘 小筆友
Been a minute, little pen pal.
阿布拉？上學
Abra? School.
好吧  我知道
Fine, I know.
嘿 爺爺 你看到羅西了嗎？
Hey, Gramps, you seen Rosie?
望塔
Watchtower.
你感覺還好嗎？
You feelin' okay?
太棒了
Peachy keen.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉 打擾了
Sorry to interrupt.
有什麼好消息嗎？
Any luck?
很接近   -嗯
- Gettin' closer. - Hmm.
我想他在愛荷華州的某個地方
He's somewhere in Iowa, I think.
一旦我確定我找到了他  我們都會進行一次愉快的長途旅行
We'll all take a nice long road trip once I'm sure I've found him.
在我做之前  我們...
Until I do, we...
你得打開一個罐子 羅西
You gotta open a canister, Rosie.
六個月前我們拿走蒸汽了  克勞  六個月不算什麼
We took steam six months ago, Crow. Six months is nothing.
特拉華州的那個孩子不是那麼性感  而且已經出現了
That kid in Delaware wasn't so steamy and it's already showing.
你看到爺爺的頭髮了嗎？
You see Grampa Flick's hair, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
我覺得他不舒服
I don't think he's well.
自從尼克松上任以來 格拉姆帕·弗利克一直不太好
Grampa Flick hasn't been well since Nixon was in office.
我知道
I know.
但我們需要吃飯  我們所有人
But we need to eat. All of us.
罐子放低了嗎？
Are the canisters low?
當然沒有
Course not.
只是不需要浪費一個  如果你接近死亡的話
Just no need to waste one if you're close to the kill.
-羅西  -嗯？
- Rosie. - Mm-hmm?
我可能需要它來找到他
I might need it just to find him.
世界上以前有更多的蒸汽 你知道嗎？
There used to be more steam in the world, you know?
別傻了 快點
Oh, don't be daft. Come on.
就像魯比斯說的
That's like when rubes say,
「50年前 人們曾經更友善 」
"50 years ago, people used to be more neighborly."
但這是真的 羅西
But it's true, Rosie.
外面的蒸汽少了 而且也變弱了
There's less steam out there, and it's weaker, too.
我不知道是因為他們的手機 還是飲食
I don't know if it's their cell phones or diets
或是他們的Netflix
or their Netflix or what,
但這些天我沒有聞到很多氣味
but I am not picking up many scents these days,
我做的那些 羅西 只是不是...
and the ones that I do, Rosie, are just not that...
今晚我會打開一個罐子讓大家都過來
I'll open a canister tonight to tide everyone over.
感謝
Thank you.
-你知道的  羅西   -我知道什麼？
- You know it, Rosie. - I know What?
所以你每天都在這裏
It's why you're up here every day.
所以不管你跟別人說什麼 你總是在這裏
It's why you're always up here no matter what you tell the others.
世界不是那麼潮濕
The world's not as steamy
你在找一隻鯨魚
and you are looking for a whale.
噢 看著這孩子 19號
Oh, watch this kid. Number 19.
那孩子是天生的
That kid is a natural.
他每次都能擊中球
He hits the ball every time.
就像他能讀懂投手的心思
Like he can read the pitcher's mind.
嗯 是這樣嗎？
Hmm. Is that right?
看到了嗎？你看 總有一天 一個天才球探
See? You watch, one of these days, one of those talent scouts
會聽到布拉德的風聲  你看著
is gonna get wind of Brad there. You watch.
嘿  19歲
Hey, 19,
剛看了你的遊戲
just saw your game.
你已經為專業做好了準備
You are ready for the majors.
-打得好   -謝謝
- Well played. - Thanks.
嘿  你回家嗎？
Hey, you headin' home?
你想跳進來嗎？我載你一程
You wanna hop in? I'll give you a ride.
不用了  真的很近
No, it's real close.
我沒事
I'm Good.
沒關係的
It's okay.
我們是朋友  你想跳進來  我們會帶你回家的
We're friends. You wanna hop in. We'll take you right home.
你可以帶我回家
You can take me right home.
你相信我
You trust me.
我相信你
I trust you.
不！不！求你了！
No! No, please! No!
不！請讓我走
No! Please let me go.
拜託  我不會說的  拜託了  求你了！
Please, I won't tell. Please. Please!
19號
Number 19.
孩子  你很棒
Kid, you were Good.
不！
No!
不 請讓我走
No, please let me go.
我不會說的 我不會說的 拜託了
I won't tell. I won't tell. Please.
沒關係的
It's okay.
求你了
Please.
啊
Ah.
你要傷害我嗎？
Are you gonna hurt me?
是的
Yes.
不！
No!
疼痛能淨化蒸汽
Pain purifies steam.
害怕  所以  你明白
Fear, too, so, you understand.
噓
Shh.
住手！
Stop!
住手  怪物
Stop, monster.
住手  住手
Stop. Stop.
是什麼？
What is it?
住手！
No! Stop!
-阿布拉！阿布拉！ -嘿 嘿 嘿！
- Abra! Abra! - Hey, hey, hey!
寶貝 寶貝 醒醒 醒醒 甜心
Sweetie. Sweetheart, wake up. Wake up, sweetheart.
-阿布拉  醒醒！-嘿  嘿  嘿
- Abra, wake up! - Hey, hey, Hey.
-打開！ 開！ -停止它！
- Abra! Abra! - Stop it!
上帝啊
Jesus.
好吧
Okay.
他媽的 我以為他還有幾分鐘
Damn. I thought he had another few minutes in him.
好了 準備好了嗎？
Okay, ready?
他們殺了他
They killed him.
沒關係的
It's okay.
我們有個旁觀者
We had a looker.
今晚？
Tonight?
嗯
Mm-Hmm.
是的
Yeah.
大蒸汽？
Big steam?
噢 親愛的 它很大
Oh, honey, it was huge.
在哪裏？
Where?
我想是東海岸
East Coast, I think.
你是說有人在1500英里外看見我們？
You're saying someone looked in from 1,500 miles away?
或許更進一步
Maybe further.
男孩還是女孩？
Boy or girl?
女孩  我想
Girl, I think.
她跑得太快了
She was out of there so fast.
但我發誓  烏鴉爸爸
But I swear, Crow Daddy,
我很久沒有那種感覺
I haven't felt power like that,
像那樣的原始力量
raw power like that
很久了
in so long.
我們得調查一下
Then we need to look into it.
-越快越好   -是的
- Sooner the better. - Yeah.
如果她父母嚇壞了
Case her parents freak out,
送她去看心理醫生
send her to a psychiatrist.
你知道 他們給她吃藥 可能會毀了蒸汽
You know, they get her on pills, could ruin the steam.
可能會讓她...
Might muffle her just...
不 把帕克斯給了這孩子
No, giving Paxil to this kid,
就像把一塊薩蘭包裹在探照燈上
it's like throwing a piece of Saran Wrap over a searchlight.
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is,
但等她回來 她就會回來
but when she comes back, and she'll be back,
我會準備好的 親愛的
oh, I'll be ready, honey.
我會準備好的
I'll be ready.
早上好
Morning.
你猜怎麼著
Guess what.
我交了個新朋友
I made a new friend.
他叫丹
His name's Dan.
是嗎？在學校？
Yeah? At school?
不是  他不住在這裏
No. He doesn't live here.
我是說  他住得很近
I mean, he lives close.
弗雷澤 我想
Frazier, I think.
沒什麼大不了的
No big deal.
阿布斯 你沒事吧？
Abs, are you okay?
昨晚 我...
Last night, I...
好吧
I'm Okay.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
我知道你的頭有時就像收音機
I know that head of yours is like a radio sometimes.
你還可以找到一些奇怪的電台
And you pick up some weird stations.
這一點都不奇怪
Nothing weird like that.
不會了
Not anymore.
上帝啊
My God.
我要學習 如果我不學習...
I've gotta study. If I don't study...
跑步遊戲 切換到11號...
Running play. Hand-off to 11 and...
如果我拿不到這些教練會殺了我的
Coach is gonna kill me if I don't get these.
他為什麼不喜歡我？
Why doesn't he like me?
我的頭髮？我應該換頭髮
My hair? I should change my hair.
怪物又盯著我看了
The freak is staring at me again.
她在看什麼？
What is she staring at?
怪胎
Freak.
嘿  阿巴杜
Hey, Abba-doo.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, Dad.
學校好嗎？
School okay?
書怎麼樣了？
How's the book?
很好  是的  進展順利
Good. Yeah, going Good.
我在寫查爾斯頓和黑底
I'm writing about Charleston and Black Bottom.
是啊 這是...
Yeah, it's...
感覺好像......我要開始做作業了
- It's feeling like... - I'm going to start my homework.
好吧  很好  很好  親愛的
Okay. Good. That's good, sweetie.
想想哈佛三年後
Think Harvard in three years.
我們拭目以待
We'll see.
是的  我們拭目以待
Yeah. We will see.
非常感謝
Thanks so much
今天和我們一起購物
for shopping with us today.
記住 我們總是新鮮的 只是為了你
And remember, we're always fresh, just for you.
好吧  你好
Well, hi there.
出去！
Get out!
出去！從我腦子裏滾出去！
Get out! Get out of my head!
出去！
Get out!
-女士 你沒事吧？ -不！沒事
- Ma'am, are you okay? - No! No.
是的  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我很好
I'm fine.
上帝啊
Jesus.
丹諾？
Danno?
丹？
Dan?
起來  站起來  丹
Get up. Stand up, Dan.
來吧 丹諾
Come on, DanNo.
-發生了什麼事？-你剛剛摔倒了
- What happened? - Well, you just dropped.
我以為你中風了 托尼是誰？
Thought you was having a stroke. Who's Tony?
What?  什麼？ What? What?
What? What? What? What?
你一直說 「請幫幫我 托尼 」
You kept saying, "Please help me, Tony."
哦
Oh.
我很抱歉
Well, I'm Sorry about that.
蘿西？
Rosie?
我們有麻煩了
We've got a problem.
-跟我說 -那個旁觀者
- Talk to me. - The looker?
是啊  她又找到我了
Yeah, she found me again.
-怎麼做到的？ -我不知道
- How? - I don't knOw.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我們得抓住她  克勞  我們必須這麼做
We have to have her, Crow. We have to.
她知道你是誰嗎？我們在哪裏？
Does she know who you are? Where we are?
不 我不知道 我不認為...這不重要...聽著
No, I don't know. I don't think... That's not the important... Look.
-我說她很有活力  對吧   -嗯哼
- I said she's huge steam, right? - Mm-Hmm.
是啊  比那還要強大
Yeah, it's even bigger than that.
我試圖控制她
I tried to turn around in her
她把我從她身上轟了出來  而且輕而易舉
and she blew me out of her like I was nothing.
-胡說  -沒有  從來沒有發生在我身上 從來沒有
- Bullshit. - No. Never happened to me, ever.
我應該說那是不可能的
I would have said that was impossible.
她是食物還是我們把她變成吸血鬼？
Is she food or do we turn her?
我們不能把她變成吸血鬼
We don't turn her.
羅西  你確定嗎？
Rosie, are you sure?
如果她就是你說的那樣 那麼...
If she's what you say she is, then...
那我們就不想讓任何人在結中擁有這種力量
Then we don't want anyone with that power in the Knot.
天啊  想想吧
Jeez. Think about it.
如果她兩個都不是呢？
What if she's neither?
你什麼意思？
What do you mean?
我是說  我們不殺她
I mean, we don't kill her.
我們不會把她變成吸血鬼
And We don't turn her.
想想一頭牛
Think of a cow.
你殺了它  只能給你一個月的肉
You butcher one, that gives you meat for a month.
讓它活著
Keep it alive,
好好照顧它
take care of it,
它可以提供給你好幾年的牛奶
it gives you milk for years.
-羅西  我們從來沒試過  -我知道
- Rosie, we've never tried that. - I know.
因為蒸汽頭是危險的
Because a steam head is dangerous.
你讓它活著  可能會很危險
You keep it alive, it could be dangerous.
我知道  關鍵是...
I know. The point...
關鍵是 克勞
The point, Crow,
她是大白鯨
is she's the great white whale.
我想要她
And I want her.
我要她
I want her.
我他媽的想要她
I fucking want her.
祝你今天愉快
Have a great day.
你也是
You, too.
嘿
Hi.
比利
Billy.
你能聽到我的聲音
You can hear me.
我們用外面的聲音  好嗎？
Let's use our outside voices, all right?
你找到我了？
You tracked me down?
這比我想像的要容易  就像GPS  但在我腦子裏
It was easier than I thought. Like GPS, but in my head.
聽著  我不是有意冒犯  但這個年代  一個成年人
Look, I don't mean any offense, but this day and age, a grown man
和一個十幾歲的女孩坐在公園的長凳上...
sitting with a teenage girl on a park bench...
我是阿布拉·斯通  如果有人問你  你是我叔叔
I'm Abra Stone. And if anyone asks, you're my uncle.
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan.
這甚至不是謊言  完全不是
And that's not even a lie. Not totally.
我們還有其他關係
We're related in other ways.
你很神奇  就像我一樣
You're magic, like me.
我不懂魔法
I don't know about magic.
我...
I...
我總是叫它閃亮
I always called it the shining.
是啊  我們都很光彩照人
And, yeah, we both shine.
你父母知道嗎？
Do your parents know?
關於我的光芒？
About my shine?
他們很害怕
They're scared of it,
但他們認為它已經消失了 除了一些東西
but they think it's gone except for a few things.
就像 我媽媽有時讓我幫她找到丟失的東西
Like, my mom sometimes asks me to help her find something she's lost.
上個月 是她的車鑰匙
Last month, it was her car keys.
她把它們丟在我爸爸車庫的工作台上
She left them on my dad's worktable in the garage.
但他們不談論這件事
But they don't talk about it.
或者如果我使用它  他們會用不同的眼光看我
Or if I use it, they look at me different.
或者什麼都不做
Or not at all.
一整天都
Not for a whole day once.
不敢直視我的眼睛
Wouldn't look me in the eYes.
所以  我盡量不用它
So, I try not to use it.
因為如果人們發現了
Because if people find out,
「伊克 一個怪胎 」你知道嗎？
"Eek, a freak." You know?
相信你知道
Sure you know.
你也盡量不要用它
You try not to use it, too.
你已經試了很久了
You've been trying a long time,
她也不看你的眼睛
and she couldn't look you in your eyes either.
當我還是個孩子的時候 我不
When I was a kid, I didn't
理解什麼光明  我叫它托尼 」
understand the shining. I called it "Tony."
我以為他是我想像中的朋友
I thought he was my imaginary friend.
我以為你是我想像中的朋友...
I thought you were my imaginary friend...
很長一段時間都這樣
for a long time.
我們有多少人在外面？
How many of us are out there?
很多人都有一點閃光點
There's a lot of people who have a little bit of shine,
他們甚至不知道
they don't even know it.
他們似乎總是帶著鮮花回家
They always seem to come home
當他們的妻子傷心的時候
with flowers when their wives are sad,
或者他們沒有學習但在學校考試上考的很好
or they do well on the school test they didn't study for.
但我只遇到兩三個人
But I only met two or three people
在我的一生當中  誰知道他們的閃光點
in my whole life who knew they shined.
棒球男孩閃光點
The baseball boy shined.
他叫布拉德利·特雷弗
His name was Bradley Trevor.
這些人...
These people...
不管怎樣 他們看起來像人 他們帶走了他
they look like people anyway, they took him.
他們吃了他
And they ate him.
他們吃了他的光
They ate his shine.
你能感覺到嗎？
You could feel it?
他們也能感覺到我
And they could feel me, I think.
他們中至少有一個做到了  一位女士
At least one of them did. A lady.
戴帽子的女士
The lady with the hat.
我想找到他們  阻止他們
I wanna find them, stop them,
因為我認為  他們也對很多其他孩子做了這種事
because I think they've done this to a lot of other kids, too.
所以 我得做點什麼 對吧？
So, I have to do something, right?
你為什麼來這裏？
Why did you come here?
為什麼是我？
Why me?
因為你能聽到我說話
Because you can hear me.
你應該相信我  你也會發光的
You'd believe me. You shine, too.
他們傷害了像我們這樣的人
And they hurt people like us.
我是說  你會怎麼做？
I mean, what would you do?
如果你能得到一些他的東西
If you could get something of his,
如果你能去愛荷華州...
if you could go to Iowa...
-喔 等等 -我可以幫你找到他
- Whoa, hang on. - I can help you find him.
然後他的父母會知道他在哪
Then his parents would know where he was.
他們至少可以把他埋起來
They could bury him right, at least.
我們還可以拿到他的手套
We could also get his glove.
如果我能摸到那隻手套  我就能追蹤他們
If I can touch that glove, I can track them.
冷靜  冷靜
Easy. Easy.
因為巴瑞 我想那是他的名字
Because Barry the Chunk, I think that was his name,
在他們殺了他之前
for a while, before they killed him,
他戴著它
he was wearing it.
阿布拉  回家吧
Abra, go home.
想想你的學校  想想你的父母
Think about your school. Think about your parents.
想想你的餘生
Think about the rest of your life.
別追這些人
Don't chase these people.
別惹他們生氣
Don't aggravate them.
不管你做什麼  都不要引起他們的注意
And whatever you do, don't attract their attention.
不要發光
Don't shine.
找到什麼 任何東西...
Find something, anything...
好吧 幾乎任何事 阻止你的光芒
Well, almost anything, to stop that shine of yours.
低著頭  保持低調  向上帝祈禱
Keep your head down, keep your shine down and hope to God
這些人或任何類似的人
that these people or anything like them,
他們就看不到你
that they don't see you.
如果他們看到你  他們就會回來
If they see you, they come back.
你聽到了嗎
Abra, do You hear me?
他們會回來
They come back.
把頭低下  注意安全
Keep your head down. Stay safe.
我很抱歉
I'm Sorry.
那一年的情況很艱難
Things were tough that year.
很多演員都失業了
A lot of actors were out of work.
嘿 夥計們
Hey, fellas.
埃爾默·富德那個雜耍明星來了
Here comes Elmer Fudd that big vaudeville star.
是什麼？
What is it?
哦 沒什麼 醫生
Oh, it's nothing, Doc.
沒什麼
It's nothing.
想著爸爸
Thinking about Dad.
不 我沒有
No, I'm not.
你就是 你不會想的
You are. And you don't want to.
別擔心我 醫生
Don't worry about me, Doc.
我很好
I'm fine.
我們很好
We're fine.
嘿 阿齊
Hey, Azzie.
今晚你的電話線路不通
You got your wires crossed tonight.
房間是空的 阿茲
That room's empty, Az.
房間裏沒有人
There's no one in that room.
哇！等等 醫生
Whoa! Hang on, Doc.
迪克
Dick.
哦 對不起
Oh, I'm so Sorry.
我...我...我以為是...
I... I... I thought it was...
我以為我是從「俯視」來的
Thought I was from the Overlook.
差點把我關起來
Almost locked me up.
還有老鬼來看他們嗎？
Still getting visits from them old ghosts?
不 好多年沒有了
No, not for years.
霍勒斯·德溫特是最後一個 他西裝上的紙屑
Horace Derwent was the last one, confetti on his suit.
說 「派對很棒 不是嗎？」
Said, "Great party, isn't it?"
我給他拿出了一個盒子 在他臉上咧著嘴大笑
Shit-eating grin on his face till I pulled out a box for him.
那笑容消失得很快
That grin went fast.
嘿 那時候我從沒想過要問你
Hey, it never occurred to me to ask you back then.
他們在那些盒子裏會發生什麼？
What happens to them in those boxes?
他們死在那兒嗎？
Do they die in there?
你在乎嗎？
Do you care?
我想你了
I missed you.
已經很久了嗎？
Has it been a long time?
不好說
Can't tell.
這個世界對我來說是一個夢
This world is a dream of a dream to me now.
八年了  再多說幾句一點
Eight years. Little more.
上次我見到你
Last time I saw you,
你在最底層
you was at the bottom.
你現在看上去不錯
You look better now.
你為什麼在這裏？
Why are you here?
我來是因為一切都來了
I'm here because it all comes 'round.
卡是個預警  醫生
Ka's a wheel, Doc.
你聽著 孩子
You listen, son.
在這裏很痛苦  所以我只說一次
It hurts to be here, so I'll only say it once.
這些空虛的魔鬼曾經找到過你
These empty devils ever found you
當你還是個孩子的時候
when you was a tyke,
如果他們發現了你
if they'd even sniffed you,
你早就死了
you'd be long dead.
它們在陸地上就像皮膚上的癌癥
They're on the land like a cancer on the skin.
有一次  他們在沙漠裏騎駱駝
Once, they rode camels in the desert.
有一次  他們駕駛大篷車穿越東歐
Once, they drove caravans across Eastern Europe.
他們吃尖叫聲
They eat screams,
喝痛苦
and drink pain,
他們注意到了那個小女孩
and they've noticed that little girl.
他們可能會殺了她
They might kill her,
可能會讓她
might turn her,
或者把她養著  直到使用完為止
or might keep her till she's all used up,
那將是非常糟糕的
and that'd be worst of all.
你不能讓他們這麼做
You can't let 'em.
為什麼是我？
Why me?
因為她找到了你
Because she found you.
因為她出現了  該死  博士  為什麼是我?
Because she showed up. Hell, Doc, Why me?
有天你剛走進我的廚房
You just walked on into my kitchen one day,
我還在忙碌著
and I'm still on the hook.
我該怎麼辦？
What the hell am I supposed to do?
給她想要的東西
Get her what she asked for.
你不會再見到我了  醫生
You won't see me again, Doc.
這是我最後的夢想
This is my last dream.
在我看來你成長的很好  孩子
It seems to me you grew up fine, son,
但你還欠著債
but you still owe a debt.
付錢吧
Pay it.
上帝啊  該死  什麼？
God, damn it. What?
抱歉  打擾了
Hey. Sorry to interrupt.
我告訴過你 「不要分心 」不是嗎？
I told you, "no distractions." Didn't I?
沒什麼吃的 沒什麼喝的
Nothing to eat, nothing to drink.
只要平靜  安靜和冥想
Just peace, quiet, and meditation.
今晚我得使出渾身解數來對付她  克魯
I need all my wits for her tonight, Crow.
所以我才在這裏 我發現了一些東西
That's why I'm here. I found something.
「地震有多小？
"How small can an earthquake be?
很小 如果裏奇蘭法院的人
Pretty small, if the people of Richland Court,
一條短的安妮斯頓街  盡頭是薩科河  是值得相信的
a short Anniston street that dead-ends at the Saco River, are to be believed.
星期二深夜
Late Tuesday night,
幾名居民報告說  街道上有震感
several residents of the street reported a tremor
窗戶和地板都有響聲
that rattled windows, shook floors,
玻璃器皿也從架子上掉了下來
and sent glassware tumbling from the shelves.
儘管在倫瑟姆的地質調查中心
Although the Geological Survey Center in Wrentham
據報道 上週二新英格蘭地區沒有發生地震 」
reports there were no temblors in New England last Tuesday."
你覺得呢？
What do you think?
我想 也許吧
I think, maybe.
我不是百分之百 但我覺得有50%
I'm not a hundred percent, but I'll take fifty-fifty.
如果那是她...
If that's actually her...
裏奇蘭法院
Richland Court.
她做到了  震動了整個新罕布什爾的街道...
She did that, shook a whole street in New Hampshire...
有一個值得關注的地方 不僅僅是一個城鎮 還有一條街道
Having a place to actually focus on, not just a town, but a street,
今晚對我來說會很輕鬆
is gonna make things a hell of a lot easier for me tonight.
做的好
Good catch.
你想怎麼對付她？
How you coming at her?
好吧  她會睡著的
Well, she'll be aSleep.
我只想四處看看 看看她是不是
I'll just wanna look around, see if she is.
像小蟲子一樣 提出一些建議
Plant some suggestions, like little worms.
讓他們去挖洞吧
Let them burrow.
一百條蟲子圍繞著她親愛的朋友 結
A hundred worms about her dear friends, the Knot.
當我們到達時
And when we roll up,
她會很高興見到我們的  她會跳上車的
she'll be so happy to see us, she'll just hop right in the van.
-如果她這麼做...-嗯？
- If she did this... - Mm-hmm?
...真的震動了整條街
...really shook a whole street,
我覺得你應該小心
I think you should be careful.
她是個小女孩
She's a little girl.
你一直都是女王婊子
And you are the queen bitch of all time.
-嗯   -我知道
- Mm. - I know.
只是說說而已
Just saying.
-小心  -嗯
- Be careful. - Mm.
嗯
Mm.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 媽媽
Hey, Mom.
你感覺還好嗎？
You feeling okay?
我們晚餐時想你了
We missed you at dinner.
我沒事 剛度過了艱難的一天
I'm okay. Just had a rough day.
我早上要飛出去看莫莫
I'm flying out to see Momo in the Morning.
我會盡快回來的
I'll be back as soon as I can.
她是不是...
Abs, is she...
她這次能挺過去嗎？
Is she gonna pull through this time?
我不知道
I don't know.
我希望能挺過去
I hope so.
告訴她我愛她
Tell her I love her.
繼續睡吧 公主
Keep sleeping, princess.
你個笨蛋
You rubes.
一輩子都在做小盒子
Spend your whole lives making little boxes,
小小的回憶
little memories.
哦  你覺得他們讓你這麼富有
Oh, you think they make you so rich.
你應該看看我的 孩子
You should see mine, kiddo.
噢 我的腦海裏是一座大教堂
Oh, my mind's a cathedral.
嘿  你好
Well, hi there.
嗯
Hmm.
他說你會回來的
He said you'd come back.
你怎麼做了
And You did.
好
Good.
不！
No!
退後！退後！
Get back! Get back!
你只是個孩子！
You're just a fucking child!
你在哪？
Where are you?
在哪裏？你在哪兒...？哪裏...？
Where? Where did you...? Where...?
你做了什麼？你在哪兒...？
What did you...? Where did you...?
不
No.
滾出去！
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
羅斯？
Rose?
陷阱
Trap.
到底發生了什麼？
What the hell happened?
-小婊子給我設了個陷阱   -天啊  你的手
- Little bitch set a trap for me. - Oh, my God. Your hand.
羅斯！羅斯 冷靜點
Rose! Rose, calm down.
我們知道她現在在哪裏  對吧？現在我們知道了
We know where she is now, right? Now we know.
她在我腦子裏！
She was in my head!
-什麼？-偷！
- What? - Stealing!
她知道什麼？
What does she know?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
她要多少錢？我不知道！
- How much does she... - I don't know!
我不知道...有個問題
- I don't know... - There's a problem.
現在不行！
Not now!
格蘭帕·弗利克...
Grampa Flick...
我想他在騎自行車
I think he's cycling.
丹叔叔！ 丹叔叔  我傷著她了
Uncle Dan! Uncle Dan, I hurt her.
我真的傷著她了
I really hurt her.
我傷著她  她活該
I hurt her and she deserved it
這不是最好的部分 最好的部分是...
and that's not the best part. The best part is...
最好的是我在她腦子裏 我進入了她的腦海
The best part is I got in her head. I got in her head.
-丹叔？你在嗎？  -天啊 阿布拉
- Uncle Dan? Are you there? - Oh, God, Abra.
你能聽到我說話嗎？
Can you hear me?
你都做了什麼？
What have you done?
去和孩子談談
Just talk to the kid.
如果我們要這麼做 那我們就這麼做
If we're gonna do this, then let's do this.
嗨 阿布拉
Hi, Abra.
我能聽到你的聲音
I can hear you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你會的
You will.
我以為我們能長生不死
I thought we lived forever.
有人承諾過你嗎 安迪？
Did someone promise you that, Andi?
有人說你是不朽的嗎？
Did someone say you're immortal?
我說 「長壽 吃得好 」
I said, "Live long, eat well."
我們可以活得很長 很長
We can live long, very long.
我們有
And we do,
我們大多數人
most of us.
但我們一直吃得不好
But we haven't been eating well.
不會很長時間
Not for a long time.
羅西 他要走了
Rosie, he's going.
蘿西
Rosie.
是的 親愛的？
Yes, love?
我很害怕
I'm scared.
不 你不用怕
No, you're not.
你看著帝國興衰
You watched empires rise and fall.
為羅馬的角鬥士歡呼
Cheered the gladiators in Rome.
在大洋彼岸航行
Sailed across oceans,
到新的世界
to new worlds,
當你養活國王、王子和教皇的時候
while you fed on kings, and princes, and popes.
他們寫了你的神話
They wrote myths of you,
並製作了雕像
and made statues,
他們在自己的村莊和床上發抖
and they trembled in their villages, and beds,
還有摩天大樓
and skyscrapers.
所以 不...
So, no...
...你不害怕
...you're not scared.
你是個國王...
You're a king...
你吃了恐懼
and you eat fear.
嘿  兄弟
Hey, bro.
你知道  現在是凌晨4點
You know, it's 4:00 a.m.
你一直都看到我  比利
You've always seen me, Billy.
你對人很有判斷力  這樣說公平嗎？
You have a good sense about people, is that fair to say?
是啊 什麼...
Yeah, what...
你覺得我是個誠實的人？一個好人？
You think I'm an honest man? A good man?
是的 我知道 丹 我...
I do, I do. Dan, I...
我需要你的幫助
I need your help.
我需要的第一件事就是  讓你聽一個故事
The first thing I need is for you to listen to a story
並且比以前更努力地相信我
and try harder than you've ever tried to believe me.
進展得怎樣？
How's it going?
哦 嘿
Oh, hey.
你不應該準備上學嗎？
Shouldn't you be getting ready for school?
是的 但我想一起去
Yeah, but I wanted to tag along.
你開車多久了？
How long have you been driving?
幾個小時左右..
A few hours or so.
我們今晚應該到那裏 一會
We should get there tonight. Late.
他是誰？
Who's that?
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
也許是我最好的朋友
Maybe my best friend.
你應該看看她的臉
You should've seen her face.
她很害怕  丹叔
She was scared, Uncle Dan.
像那些孩子一樣害怕
Scared like all those kids were scared.
她殺的那些孩子
All those kids she's killed.
她太生氣了 太害怕了 我進去了
She was so mad and so scared that I got in.
這是一個新的把戲
That was a new trick.
我以前從沒這麼做過
I've never done that before.
是啊 我也是 是什麼感覺？
Yeah, me neither. What was it like?
就像圖書館
Like a library.
我想我們都是裏面的圖書
I guess we're all libraries inside.
你怎麼做到的？
How'd you do it?
像這樣 只是稍微推一下
Like this. Just a little push.
阿布拉！
Abra!
對不起！對不起 對不起 對不起！
Sorry! Sorry, sorry, sorry!
-對不起  我不是故意的  -沒關係
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. - It's okay.
那些箱子都是什麼？
What were all those boxes?
什麼都沒有
Nothing.
撒謊
Liar.
我小時候
When I was a kid,
我比你年輕的時候  遇到了類似的事情
younger than you, I bumped into something like these things
就像他們吃的那樣
that ate like they do.
但那不是一個人  而是一個地方
Only it wasn't a person, it was a place.
他們把它關起來 讓它腐爛
They closed it down after and let it rot.
但是生活在那裏的東西 他們...
But the things that lived there, they...
別再到那兒來找我了
Don't go poking around in there again.
好吧 我不會的 我保證
Okay, I won't. I promise.
我們差不多準備好了 我們只是在裝貨
We're almost ready. We're just loading up.
好
Good.
把商隊弄到路上
Get the caravan on the road
我們一兩天就能見到她
and we'll have her in a day or two.
我覺得你不該來  羅西
I don't think you should come, Rosie.
你剛才他媽的說什麼？
The fuck did you just say?
她給你貼了標籤
She tagged you.
她進入了你的大腦
She got in your head.
是啊 不會再發生了
Yeah, it won't happen again.
誰知道在你把她趕出去之前  她還瞭解多少
And who knows how much she got to before you kicked her out.
她是我的 克魯 噢
She's mine, Crow.
據我們所知 現在
Right now, as far as we know,
你是她唯一能追蹤的人
you are the only one of us she could track.
如果她看到你來
Now, if she sees you coming,
她可以跑
she could run
或者設置另一個陷阱
or set another Trap.
我要把她打昏
I will knock her out cold.
國安局的一名線人給了我有用的信息
One of our assets from the NSA gave me the good stuff.
把她趕出去  別讓她吸毒過量
Put her out without chance of an overdose.
我往南走  繞一圈
I'll head south. I'll circle around.
我會從另一個方向來找她
I'll come at her from a different direction.
我應該在那裏
I should be There.
你知道我是對的
You know I'm right about this.
好吧
Okay.
如果你願意 我會把安迪留在這裏
I'll leave Andi here with you, if you want.
不 不 你們都需要力量
No, no, you'll need your strength, all of you.
如果她耍了你
If she pulls a trick on you,
就同歸於盡
stay together.
-嗯  -嗯
- Yeah? - Mm-Hmm.
嗯
Mm-Hmm.
但我有自己的把戲
But I got some tricks of my own.
嘿 我想我們來了
Hey, I think we're here.
好吧
Okay.
我去看看能不能找到她
I'll see if I can get her.
阿布拉？
Abra?
這就是標誌 往後拉
That's the sign. Pull around back.
她說把車開回去
She says to pull around back.
我會告訴你什麼時候停下來
And I'll tell you when to Stop.
她會告訴我們什麼時候停下來
She'll tell us when to Stop.
我要告訴你 丹諾
I gotta tell you, Danno,
我不知道我希望你是對的還是錯的
I don't know whether I hope you're right or wrong about this.
我是說 如果你錯了 我的朋友就瘋了
I mean, if you're wrong, my friend is crazy.
我是說 全面的精神崩潰
I mean, full-blown, mental breakdown,
虛構的-怪物-殺戮-想像的-孩子
imaginary-monsters- killing-imaginary-kids
癮君子
bonkers.
但是你知道我...我可以用這個
But, you know, I... I can work with that.
如果你是對的...
If you're right, though...
我知道
I know.
更糟糕了
It's much worse.
你應該回家
You should go home.
什麼？
What?
不  不是你
No, not you.
我能搞定
I can handle it.
不是  我們會從這裏拿走的
No. We'll take it from here.
好吧 只有我們倆
Okay, it's just us.
你聞到了嗎？
You smell that?
以前是打獵的 我告訴過你嗎？
Used to hunt. I ever tell you that?
不
No.
鹿
Deer.
在這個夏天
This one summer,
我夾住了這只雄鹿
I clipped this buck.
我追蹤了兩天
I was tracking it for two days.
我打中了  夾住了他
I got the shot, clipped him.
他掙脫了  我去追
He ran off, I went after.
我以為他堅持不了多久
Figured he wasn't gonna last long.
然後他消失了
Then he vanished.
剛剛升起來蒸發了
Just up and evaporated.
一點痕跡也沒有  真是莫名其妙
Not a trace. Truly baffling.
五天後
Five days later,
我在嘗試一個不同的地方 幾英里外
I'm trying a different spot, miles away.
我到處找盲點痕跡的地方
I come around looking for a spot for a blind...
然後我聞到了他的味道
then I smelled him.
聞著他的味道
Smelled him.
找到那只雄鹿
Found that buck
窩在一個空心的樹幹上
holed up to a hollow trunk,
已經死了好幾天了
dead for days.
有股味道...
The smell...
從那以後再也沒去打過獵
Never hunted a day since.
這次是同樣的味道
This is the same smell.
比利
Billy.
哦 天哪！
Oh, my God!
他媽的
Fuck.
他媽的 丹諾 他媽的怎麼回事？
Fuck, Danno. What the fuck?
他們甚至沒有把他埋得很深  他們埋的很淺
They didn't even bury him deep. They buried him shallow.
抱歉  比利
I'm sorry, Billy.
你讓我們陷入了什麼？
What did you get us into?
做這件事的人...
The people who did that...
他們不是人
They're not people.
不是 不 他們不是
No. No, they ain't.
任何人對一個小男孩那樣做
Anyone do that to a little boy,
他們不是人
they ain't people.
你找到了嗎？
Did you get it?
是的 我們找到了
Yeah, we got it.
她回來了嗎？
Is she back?
我們要回到你身邊  我們早上就回來
We're heading back to you. We'll be back in the Morning.
我們得停下來
We got a stop to make.
我要你告訴你父母發生了什麼
I need you to show your parents what's happening.
不行
No.
-不行  他們認為我很正常
- No. They almost think I'm normal.
如果我告訴他們 他們會...
If I tell them, they'll...
羅斯會通過他們找到你的
Rose'll go through them to get to you.
你知道的 不是嗎？
You know that, don't you?
她會不假思索的殺掉他們
She'll cut them down without a second thought.
她來了 阿布拉
And she's coming, Abra.
他們需要知道
They need to know.
所以 我們要做什麼？
So, what's this stop we gotta make?
你還有那些舊的獵鹿槍嗎？
You still got those old deer rifles?
你是丹叔叔嗎？
You're Uncle Dan?
-你他媽的以為你是？-先生...
- The fuck you think you are? - Sir...
嗯？嗯？她已經13歲了！！
Hmm? Hmm? She is 13 years old!
阿布拉 我讓你給他看的
Abra, I told you to show him.
-我告訴他了 -嗯 那不一樣
- I told him. - Well, that's not the same.
在我報警之前  我要揍你一頓 嗯？
I'm gonna kick your ass before I call the police, huh?
-嘿 嘿 嘿！-不 不 不阿布拉
- Hey, hey, hey! - No, no, no. Abra.
現在 別說她的名字
Now, don't you say her name.
阿布拉...
Abra...
對不起 斯通先生 我是朋友
I'm sorry, Mr. Stone. I am a friend.
她告訴你的一切都是真的
Everything she told you is true.
到底發生了什麼？
What the hell is happening?
對不起
I'm Sorry.
阿布拉需要給你看點東西
Abra needs to show you something.
我看到那個男孩了
I saw the boy.
我看到了他的屍體
I saw his body.
一切都是真的
It's all true.
可能 你的朋友把他放在那兒了
Probably, your friend here put him There.
你想過嗎？
You think about that?
不會很久的 我沒有
Not for long, I didn't.
斯通先生 你女兒很特別
Mr. Stone, your daughter is special.
不要談論她
Don't talk about her.
我想你知道 在內心深處
I think you know that. Deep down.
她知道那個小男孩出了什麼事
She knows what happened to that little boy,
她知道是誰幹的
and she knows who did it.
給他看
Show him.
對不起 爸爸
I'm sorry, Daddy.
我真的不想
I really didn't want to.
不想什麼？
Didn't want to What?
不了 謝謝
No, thanks.
不用了
No.
那些人...
Those people...
他們知道我女兒的事嗎？
they know about my daughter?
是的
They do.
他們遲早會來的
And sooner or later, they're coming.
我們得做點什麼
We gotta do something.
好吧  我們要報警  聯邦調查局...
All right, we're calling the police, the FBI...
這些人已經存在很久了 長官
These people have been around a long, long time, sir.
他們很有錢 很有關係
They're rich, connected.
我不認為他們會擔心警察
I don't think they're worried about the police.
但他們在哪裏？
But where are they?
他們什麼時候來？我們能去哪裏？
When are they coming? Where can we go?
阿布拉可以回答...
Abra can answer that...
她準備好了
if She's ready.
我準備好了
I'm ready.
你真的想這麼做嗎？
You sure you wanna do this?
我不得不這麼做
I have to.
95號州際公路
I-95.
巴裏 烏鴉 蛇和其他一些人
Barry, the Crow, the Snake, and a few others.
樹的變化不大
The trees haven't changed that much,
所以也許是馬薩諸塞州
so maybe Massachusetts,
-但他們很接近 -羅斯？
- but they're close. - Rose?
沒看到她
Didn't see her.
但他們來了
But they're coming.
這是她唯一看到的房間？？
This is the only room she saw?
是的
That's right.
我做了一些改變 藏了些東西
And I made a few changes. Hid a few things.
好吧
All Right.
嗯 他們會試圖追蹤你
Well, they'll be trying to track you,
試圖趕上
trying to catch on.
你就讓他們這麼做
And you're gonna let them.
你瘋了嗎？
Are you crazy?
可能吧  但你就讓他們這麼做
Possibly, but you're gonna let them.
然後我需要你試著做這個小把戲
And then I need you to try and do a little trick.
一個魔術？
A magic trick?
他們在跟蹤我們
They're following us.
集中精力 你得堅持到他們找到這兒
Concentrate. You gotta keep it up until they land.
我知道
I know.
這應該行得通
This should work.
好的百葉窗在那邊  還有那裏
Good blinds over there, and There.
他們還在附近？
They still close?
我想 越來越近了
Getting closer, I think.
這很艱難
This is tough.
我知道 我知道 不會太久了
I know. I know. Not much longer.
好吧 烏鴉爸爸
Okay, Crow Daddy,
去找她
go get her.
你看起來很放鬆
You look relaxed.
你感覺很放鬆  是吧  阿巴拉
You feel relaxed, don't you, Abra?
我想是吧
I guess.
你應該
You should.
別緊張
Just relax.
我們是朋友
We're friends.
你們是朋友
You're friends.
是的
That's right.
只是朋友
Just friends.
我們想帶你去見更多的朋友
And we want to take you to meet more friends.
好朋友
Good friends.
哦 媽的
Well, shit.
就像他們告訴你的那樣
The way they talked you up,
我在想會不會更難一點
I was thinking it'd be a little harder than that.
他媽的？
The fuck?
把戲  只不過是他媽的惡作劇罷了
Parlor tricks. Just fuckin' parlor tricks.
不！快離開這兒
No! Get out of there!
快離開這兒
Get out of there!
不！
No!
你活該
You deserve it.
你活該 你們所有人
You deserve it. All of you.
不！
No!
他媽的
Oh, Fuck.
住手
Stop.
我只有一個問題要問你 親愛的
I just got one question for you, sweetie.
你不睏嗎？
Aren't you sleepy?
你很困
You're sleepy.
睡吧
Sleep.
快醒醒！丹叔叔！
Wake up! Uncle Dan!
快醒醒！快醒醒
Wake up! Wake up.
快醒醒！
Wake up!
他媽的男人
Fucking men.
後退  比利
Stay back, Billy.
殺了你自己
Kill yourself.
不！
No!
比利！
Billy!
少了一個
There is one missing.
我沒看到烏鴉 烏鴉在哪裏？
I didn't see the Crow. Where is the Crow?
你好 阿布拉
Hello, Abra.
阿布拉！
Abra!
離她遠點
Get away from her.
後退
Step back.
當然 爸爸
Sure thing, Dad.
很高興見到你
You know, I'm glad I got to meet you.
我他媽的會殺了你  後退
I'll fucking kill you. Step back.
一些勇敢的詞兒
Some brave words.
看著你們這些鄉巴佬威脅上帝  我總是覺得很好笑
Always tickles me, watching you rubes threaten a god.
你知道 你的小女兒
You know, your little girl,
她也許是我們最好的食物
she's maybe the best food we'll ever have.
我很高興我有機會讚美廚師
I'm so glad I had a chance to compliment the chef.
很好 你醒了
Oh, good, you're awake.
丹...
Dan...
別費心了
Don't bother.
我怎麼了？
What's wrong with me?
你吃過藥了 小姐
You've been dosed, missy.
比我以前用過的都多
More than I've ever used before.
可能會讓你在這裏或者那裏醒來
Might let you wake up here and there,
但你的蒸汽很快  睡吧
but that steam of yours is fast aSleep.
我的爸爸
My dad...
我爸怎麼了？
What happened to my dad?
今天很多好人被殺了
Lot of good people killed today.
很多好人
Lot of good people.
我很想告訴你有人會付出代價
I'd love to tell you someone will pay,
在今天的悲慘事件  中出現了某種正義感
some kind of justice raining down on the sad events today,
但它不是那樣運作的
but it don't work like that.
我們會一直擁有你的
We were always gonna have you.
我的一些人死了
Some of my people are dead.
你的有些人死了
Some of yours are dead.
但結果並沒有改變
Outcome didn't change, though.
仔細想想
Think on that a minute.
結果沒有改變
The outcome didn't change.
所以  他們的死
So, their deaths,
所有的人
all of them,
只是一種浪費
just a waste.
你帶來的浪費
A waste you brought on
敬我們大家  小姐
to us all, young lady.
為了什麼？
For What?
聽我說...
Please hear me...
沒人聽到你說話
Ain't nobody hearing you.
不妨冷靜一下 好好享受這段旅程
Might as well calm down and enjoy the ride.
就像我說的
Like I said,
結果沒有改變
outcome hasn't changed.
不
No.
拜託
Please.
噢 拜託 拜託 拜託
Oh, please, please, Please.
拜託
Please.
阿布拉！
Abra!
阿布拉
Abra.
托尼？
Tony?
幫幫我 托尼
Help me, please, Tony.
上帝啊
God.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
Okay, Okay.
好吧 你總是說...
Okay, you always said...
你的大腦就像收音機
your brain was like a radio.
你打電話的時候沒人接 所以別打了
No one's answering when you call, so stop calling.
聽著
And just listen.
丹  丹
Dan. Dan.
幫幫我
Help.
嘿
Hi.
丹
Dan.
他給你下藥了嗎？
Did he drug you?
我很抱歉
I'm so Sorry.
我想試試看 好嗎？
I'm gonna try something, okay?
但你很虛弱
But you're weak.
他在阻止你
He's blocking you.
我幾乎聽不見你說話
I could barely hear you.
你要相信我 好嗎？
You gotta trust me, okay?
好嗎？
Okay?
又醒了 是吧？
Awake again, huh?
可能得在下次休息的時候給你下藥
Might have to dose you at the next rest Stop.
我們要去哪裏？
Where are we going?
嗯 你知道在哪
Mm, you know where.
他媽的 我感覺宿醉
Fuck, I feel hungover.
我告訴過你這是好東西
I told you it's good shit.
好多年沒宿醉了 你知道 我不會錯過的
Haven't felt hungover in years. And, you know, I don't miss it.
一點也沒有
Not even a little.
西部 哈？
West, huh?
遠離大路  很聰明
Stayin' off the major roads. Smart.
克朗維爾  紐約
Crownville. New York.
你是誰
Who are you?
我是殺了你朋友的人
I'm the guy that killed your friends.
很高興見到你
It's nice to meet you.
不錯的詭計
Neat trick.
以前沒見過這個
Haven't seen this one before.
想再看一個嗎？
Wanna see one more?
不要以為羅斯會高興  如果你對獎品開槍
Don't imagine Rose'll be too happy if you shoot the prize.
我想羅斯不會為這件事高興的
I don't suppose Rose will be happy about any of this.
當那個女人生氣的時候...
And when that woman gets mad...
嗯 在我看來你知道的夠多了
Well, it seems to me you know enough
你可能想置身事外
to know you might wanna sit this one out.
算是你的福氣吧
Count your blessings.
你走吧
Go on your way.
有什麼好笑的 朋友？
What's so funny, friend?
好吧 這只是傲慢 這是傲慢 真的
Well, it's just arrogance. It's arrogance, really.
但這是有道理的 如果你認為你會永生
But it makes sense, if you think you're gonna live forever.
有道理  你當然不會系安全帶
Stands to reason, of course you wouldn't wear your seatbelt.
不！
No!
丹？
Dan?
我希望這很痛
I hope that hurts.
羅西
Rosie...
很疼
A lot.
你個小婊子
You little bitch.
你做了什麼？
What have you done?
好吧 婊子養的
All right, bitch child.
好吧
All Right.
對不起
Sorry.
打瞌睡了
Dozed off.
不  你應該休息
No, you earned it.
我們在哪？
Where are we?
俄亥俄州
Ohio.
我們要去哪裏？
Where are we going?
科羅拉多
Colorado.
為什麼科羅拉多？
Why Colorado?
她會再來的
She's gonna keep coming.
-我知道 -永無休止
- I know. - Always.
如果我們結束了這一切
This only ends if we end it,
我不認為我們能打敗她
and I don't think we can beat her.
不是我們自己
Not by ourselves.
有個地方
There's a place.
對我們這樣的人來說很危險的地方
A place that's dangerous for people like us.
你告訴我的那個地方？飢餓的地方？
The place you told me about? The hungry place?
是的  沒錯
Yeah, That's right.
如果這麼危險 我們為什麼要去那裏？
If it's so dangerous, why would we go there?
如果對我們這樣的人來說很危險
Well, if it's dangerous for people like us,
我想對像她這樣的人 也是很危險的
I expect it's dangerous for people like her.
也許更是嚴重
Maybe even more so.
好的
Good.
她在跟蹤我們  你知道的
She's following us, you know.
是的  很好  讓她這麼做吧
Yeah, good. Let her.
你父親的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about your father.
很抱歉你的朋友
Sorry about your friend.
是我媽媽
It's my mom.
我該對她說什麼？
What do I say to her?
嗨 媽媽
Hi, Mom.
噢 感謝上帝！
Oh, thank God!
阿布拉...
Abra...
你還好嗎？ 你在哪？
Are you okay? Where are you?
我愛你
I love you.
當我們安全後  你打電話給她  告訴她在哪裏能找到我們
When we're safe, you'll call her and tell her where to find us?
我會的
I will.
好吧
Okay.
不會太遠了  上山
Not too much further. Up the mountain.
我們要做的就是
Here's what we're gonna do.
你要呆在車裏  讓暖氣開著
You're gonna stay in the car, keep the heater running.
我不想你在裏面呆一分鐘 如果你不需要的話
I don't want you spending a minute inside there if you don't have to.
她只能從這裏來..
She can only come from here.
你很容易就能看到她
You can see her a mile out, easy.
你看到那邊山上的燈光
You see lights on the mountain over there,
對我放衝擊波  好嗎？
you blast me, Okay?
但我不想讓你進去  在她來之前
But I don't want you going in. Not until she's here.
你不是在等我嗎？
You aren't waiting with me?
我做不到
I can't.
為什麼不呢？
Why not?
我得把它弄醒
I have to wake it up.
醒來  醒來
Wakey-wakey.
晚安  托倫斯先生
Slow night, Mr. Torrance.
不會太久的  我想
Not for long, I imagine.
你是個威士忌的人 不是嗎？
You're a whiskey man, are you not?
我是  大部分時間都是
I was, most of the time.
在房子裏
On the house.
這是你的牌子
This was your brand.
傑克·丹尼爾的
Jack Daniel's.
我以前在家裏看過瓶子
I used to see the bottles in our home.
我們真正的家 在這一切之前
Our real home, before all this.
我聞過一次 聞起來好像著火了
I smelled one once. It smelled like something on fire,
我想是的
which I suppose it was.
恐怕你把我和別人搞混了
I'm afraid you've confused me with someone else.
我是勞埃德
It's Lloyd.
勞埃德
Lloyd.
抱歉 托倫斯先生
I apologize, Mr. Torrance.
我不知道每個人都在哪兒  但它會回來的
I don't know where everyone is, but it'll pick up.
噢 我知道他們在哪
Oh, I know where they are.
你說得對...
And you're right...
它會回來的
it'll pick up.
如果你不介意的話 托倫斯先生 你看起來...
If you don't mind my saying, Mr. Torrance, you seem...
被利用
put upon.
被利用？
Put upon?
不是這樣的
Ain't that the way.
人們只是過著自己的生活
Man just living his life,
試著做他的工作
trying to do his work.
他被利用
He gets put upon.
捲入了別人的問題..
Pulled into other people's problems.
如果你不介意的話  我經常看到它
I see it all the time, if you don't mind my saying.
所以我們住在佛羅里達
So we lived in Florida.
不好意思？
I'm sorry?
媽媽和我
Mom and I.
恐怕我不知道你的意思是誰
I'm afraid I don't know who you mean.
我們再也不想看到雪了
We never wanted to see snow again,
所以我們住在佛羅里達
So we lived in Florida.
很小的地方 但很舒服 我們很開心
Tiny place, but it was comfortable, and we were happy.
我是說 我們很傷心
I mean, we were grieving.
我們受到了創傷
We were traumatized,
但也有幸福
but there was happiness too.
她...
She...
她會把目光移開
She would look away.
她會看著我  但她總是在一兩秒鐘後移開視線
She'd look at me, but she'd always look away after a second or two.
我花了一段時間才注意到這一點
It took me a while to notice it.
但是在看完之後  她不會看我的眼睛
But after the Overlook, she wouldn't look me in the eyes,
不會太久
not for long.
我搞不懂
Couldn't figure it out.
但它...
But it...
是你
It was you.
她在我身上看到了你的眼睛 她不得不把目光移開
She saw your eyes in me, and she'd have to look away.
她不得不這麼做 這讓她很痛苦
It tortured her to have to do that.
所以 我修補它
So, I fixed it.
我幫她修復這一點  這是我最後一次用它了
I fixed it for her, and it was the last time I ever used it.
好讓她看著我的時候不再見到你
So that she wouldn't see you anymore when she looked at me.
她死的時候我才20歲
I was 20 when she died.
當時 我看到有人要死了
And back then, I saw when someone was gonna die.
我看到蒼蠅了 黑色的蒼蠅
I saw flies. Black flies.
「死蒼蠅」 我叫他們 圍著人們的臉轉
"Death flies," I called them, circling people's faces.
在過去的幾周裏 她被...
And in those last weeks, she was covered...
她的整個臉
Her whole face.
我幾乎看不見她的眼睛
I could barely see her eYes.
我也...我試圖安慰她 但我幾乎看不見她
And I... I tried to comfort her, but I could hardly look at her.
她看到了
And she saw that.
她就躺在那兒等死
She just lay there dying,
她的兒子看不見她
with her son who couldn't look at her.
也許一些溫暖的東西可以消除這些不愉快
Maybe something warm to push away such unpleasantries.
你不想聽聽嗎？她是你的妻子
Don't you wanna hear about it? She was your wife.
我覺得你把我當成了別人
I think you've mistaken me for someone else.
-我只是個酒保  -哦 是嗎？
- I'm just a bartender. - Oh, yeah?
只有勞埃德酒保 在俯瞰酒店傾倒喜悅
Just Lloyd the bartender, pouring joy at the Overlook Hotel.
我給你倒任何你喜歡的東西 托倫斯先生
I'll pour whatever you like, Mr. Torrance.
哦 爸爸
Oh, Dad.
這種飲料要花很多錢
This drink will cost an awful lot.
你的錢在這裏不好用
Your money is no good here.
房子裏的規定
Orders from the house.
比錢還要貴
It'll cost more than money.
我要花八年時間
It'll cost me eight years.
八個人在我後面 誰知道前面有多少人
Eight behind me, and who knows how many in front of me.
你的信用很好 托倫斯先生
Your credit is fine, Mr. Torrance.
男人喝一杯
Man takes a drink,
這飲料需要喝一杯
the drink takes a drink,
然後這杯酒帶走了一個人
and then the drink takes a man.
不是嗎 爸爸？
Ain't it so, Dad?
醫藥
Medicine.
醫藥就是它的本質
Medicine is what It is.
善意的治療方法
Bona fide cure-all.
抑鬱 壓力 悔恨 失敗 把一切都抹去
Depression, stress, remorse, failure, wipes it all away.
心靈是一塊黑板..
The mind is a blackboard.
以及這個
And this
是橡皮擦
is the eraser.
一個人嘗試
A man tries.
他提供了
He provides.
但他被嘴巴包圍了
But he's surrounded by mouths.
吃 尖叫 哭泣 嘮叨
that eat, and scream, and cry, and nag.
所以 他要求一件事 只是給他一件事
So, he asks for one thing, just one thing for him.
把他暖和起來...
To warm him up...
從那些日子的嘴裏取出毒刺
to take the sting out of those days of the mouths,
吃 吃 吃 吃他做的一切
eating, and eating, and eating everything he makes,
他所擁有的一切
everything he has.
以及一個家庭
And a family.
一個妻子 一個孩子
A wife, a kid.
那些嘴吃時間
Those mouths eat time.
他們吃了你在地球上的日子
They eat your days on Earth.
他們只是狼吞虎嚥
They just gobble them up.
這足以使一個人生病
It's enough to make a man sick.
以及這個...
And this...
是醫藥
is the Medicine.
告訴我 小狗
So, tell me, pup,
你要吃藥嗎？
are you gonna take your medicine?
我不是
I'm not.
哦
Oh.
你看 我很抱歉
Look at that. I'm Sorry.
我老糊塗了 托倫斯先生 原諒我
Clumsy old me, Mr. Torrance. Forgive me.
把你清理一下
Let's get you cleaned up.
管理層感到擔心
Management is concerned.
擔心嗎？
Concerned?
她對你做的事太可怕了
It's horrible what she's done to you.
把你弄得一團糟
Pulled you into her mess.
一個聰明人？
A smart man?
他會讓她來處理的
He'd let her handle it.
順其自然吧
Let things unfold as they're meant to.
你為什麼要為她付出  醫生？
Why should you pay her tab, Doc?
為了什麼？
And For What?
為了這個  惹了這麼多麻煩的小女孩？
For this little girl who started all this trouble?
管理層會讓我做些什麼？
What would management have me do about that?
什麼都沒有
Nothing.
世上最容易做的事 孩子
Easiest thing in the world to do, son.
把她帶進去
Just bring her inside.
然後 嗯
And then, well,
接受你不能改變的事情
you accept the things you cannot change.
丹！
Dan!
她來了
She's here.
好吧
Okay.
這個地方病了
This place is sick.
就像我媽媽生病一樣
Sick like my momo was sick.
是癌癥
It's cancer,
只會更糟
only worse.
我們現在做什麼？
What do we do now?
我們進去 她會找到我們的
We head inside. She'll find us.
好 好 好
Well, well, well.
你好啊
Hi There.
開始的時候  快跑
When this starts, run.
是的 你跑吧 親愛的
Yes, you run, dear.
然後我會找到你
And then I will find you
你會尖叫很多年  直到你死
and you will scream for years until you die.
我們會看到誰在尖叫
We'll see who does the screaming.
噢 我們會看到的
Oh, we'll see indeed.
她是對的 你知道的
She's right, you know.
你應該害怕
You should be afraid.
為什麼？
Why is that?
因為你不知道你站在哪裏
Because you don't know where you're standing.
對不起 你是誰 帥哥？
I'm sorry, who are you, handsome?
是你殺了我的烏鴉  不是嗎？
You're the one who killed my Crow, aren't you?
走
Go.
很聰明
Clever.
你做了一些改進 不是嗎？
You've made some improvements, haven't you?
從上次我在你腦海裏
Since the last time I was in your mind.
你怎麼知道我們不在你家？
How do you know we're not in yours?
你在哪裏 小狗？
Where are you, pup?
你會死在這裏
You're gonna die here.
嗯  詞兒很勇敢  親愛的
Mm. Brave words, dear.
你真的這麼想嗎？
Is that what you really think?
你要傷害我？
You're gonna hurt me?
是的
Yes.
你讓我想起了我自己
You know, you remind me of myself.
我現在真的看到了
I can really see it now.
你內心深處有黑暗 親愛的
You've got a darkness in you, dear.
我想你和我唯一的區別就是時間
I think the only difference between you and me is time.
你還不知道...
You don't know yet...
你要做什麼...
what you'd do...
更多的時間
for more time.
但我向你保證 親愛的 哦 你會很驚訝的
But I promise you, dear, oh, you'd be surprised.
疼痛能淨化蒸汽
Pain purifies steam.
害怕也是  所以  你明白
Fear, too, so, you understand.
我年輕的時候和你一樣
I was just like you when I was younger.
我很特別
I was special
隻身一人
and alone.
但我遇到了一個人  他給了我目標  社區的禮物
But I met someone who gave me the gift of purpose, of community.
我也許會給你這樣的禮物
And I might have given you such a gift
如果事情有不同的發展
if things would have gone differently.
不是嗎？
No?
挑釁  不是嗎
Defiant, aren't you?
很像我
So much like me.
你想的是
Your mind is So...
這不是你的想法  對吧？
This isn't your mind, is it?
這根本不是你
This isn't you at all.
你只是誘餌
You're just the bait.
夠了！
Enough!
跑
Run.
我們怎麼會想你？
How the hell did we miss you?
哦...
Oh...
你和我幾年前就該認識了
You and I should have met years aGo.
丹尼
Danny.
這是你的名字 不是嗎？
That's your name, isn't it?
嗯 當你的皮膚變老時 蒸汽會發生一些事情
Well, something happens to the steam when you rubes get older.
它被污染了
It gets polluted.
很髒
Dirty.
你知道的
You know that.
我看到你全身都是油脂
I see the grease all over you.
你的光芒不大一樣
You don't shine quite the same.
我想  長大後會毀了這一切
Growing up spoils that, I guess.
我說真的 帥哥
Seriously, handsome,
你一直躲在哪裏？
where have you been hiding?
我可以給你一個提議
I can make you an offer.
我很少提出這個提議
An offer I rarely make.
噢 是嗎？我等不及了
Oh, yeah? I can't wait.
如此有天賦的男孩
Such a gifted boy
把他的光隱藏了這麼久
hiding his light under a bushel for so long.
你可以活很久 很久 活得也很好
You could live a long, long time. Live well, too.
放縱自己 不會有任何後果
Indulge yourself, no consequences,
沒有宿醉
no hangovers.
吃得好 活得久..
Eat well, live long.
你一定很孤獨 是最後一個
You must be lonely, being the last one.
我是說 世界上最後一個
I mean, the last one in the world.
寶貝 我不是最後一個 遠非如此
Sweetie, I'm not the last. Far from it.
我是最漂亮的
I'm just the prettiest.
我想你知道我的答案
I assume you know my answer.
可憐
Pity.
所以 我們到底要不要這麼做？
So, are we doing this or not?
咻
Whew.
哦 甜心
Oh, sweetie.
哦 看看這個 嗯？
Oh, look at that, huh?
我好像割斷了你的股動脈
I seem to have nicked your femoral artery There.
為什麼 你會流血致死 是吧？
Why, you're gonna bleed to death, huh?
天哪  天哪  你真有脾氣
My, my, what a temper you have.
太火了
So much fire.
太浪費了！
Such a waste!
或者不是
Or maybe not.
噢  該死
Oh, damn.
即使在你這個年紀...
Even at your age...
太好了
it's so Good.
你嘗起來像威士忌
You taste like whiskey.
丹尼！
Danny!
丹尼小子！
Danny boy!
哦 太恐怖了
Oh, so much terror.
一輩子 嗯？
All your life, huh?
美味
Delicious.
別傷害我！
Don't hurt me!
噢  該死
Oh, damn.
什麼......你在哪兒並不孤單
What are... You're not alone in There.
啊？
Huh?
你在隱藏什麼
What are you hiding, Huh?
裏面有什麼？
What's in those?
有什麼特殊的東西
Something special, Huh?
他們不特別  他們很餓
They're not special. They're starving.
不
No.
不！
No!
丹尼
Hello, Danny.
過來和我們一起玩...
Come and play with us...
永遠...
forever...
...永遠...
...and ever...
永遠
and ever.
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan.
丹叔  完成了嗎？
Uncle Dan, is it done?
她死了嗎？
Is she dead?
很棒的派對  不是嗎？
Great party, isn't it?
阿布拉！
Abra!
試試看
Try it.
哦  你在這兒
Oh, There you are.
阿布拉
Abra.
你一直非常非常糟糕
You've been very, very bad.
你不是丹叔叔
You're not Uncle Dan.
你是個面具 一張假臉
You're a mask. A false face.
我還會是誰？
Who else would I be?
你就是酒店
You're the hotel.
但他還在裏面
But he's still in There.
所以面具就沒了
Mask is off, then.
你為什麼笑？
Why are you smiling?
因為你不知道你站在哪裏
Because you don't know where you're standing.
我知道這些大廳就像我自己的臉 孩子
I know these halls like my own face, child.
我是說你站在裏面的屍體
I mean the body you're standing in.
你戴的那張臉
The face you're wearing.
那是丹·托倫斯 你不認識他
That's Dan Torrance, and you don't know him.
丹·托倫斯
Dan Torrance.
丹·托倫斯一到這裏就停了下來
Dan Torrance made one stop as soon as he got here.
到鍋爐房..
To the boiler room.
你回來了
There you are.
你應該跑的
You were supposed to Run.
我不想離開你
I didn't wanna leave you.
我就在我該去的地方
I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
我再也受不了了 阿布拉 你得快跑
I can't hold it off for much longer. Abra, you need to Run.
不
No.
沒有你我哪兒也去不了
I'm not going anywhere without you.
我得把門關上 對吧？
I have to close the door behind us, right?
跑啊！ 跑啊！
Run! Run!
快點  丹叔叔
Come on, Uncle Dan.
離開那裏
Get out of There.
快點
Come on.
火勢蔓延得很快
The fire spread fast,
摧毀了酒店
destroying the hotel.
淨化了它
Purifying it.
我幾乎能聽到...
I could almost hear it...
尖叫
screaming.
我能聽到它快死了
I could hear it dying.
在內心深處 我知道...
And deep inside, I knew...
我就知道你沒事
I knew you were Okay.
很抱歉我把你置於危險之中
I'm sorry I put you in danger.
這是唯一的辦法
It was the only way.
我知道
I know.
你覺得她是對的嗎
Do you think she was right
她說她不是最後一個？
when she said she wasn't the last one?
世界是個飢餓的地方
The World's a hungry place.
一個黑暗的地方
A dark place.
也許有更多像他們那樣的人  或者更糟
Maybe there's more of them or things like them or worse,
但是也有更多像你這樣的人
but there are more people like You, too.
站著的人
People who stand.
我第一次見你的時候告訴過你
I told you when I first met you,
我告訴過你你應該躲起來
I told you that you should hide.
你應該保持低調
That you should keep your head down.
別讓人看到你的光芒
Keep your shine out of sight.
但我錯了
But I was wrong.
閃耀吧  阿布拉·斯通
Shine on, Abra Stone.
你的光芒
You shine on.
晚餐準備好了
Dinner's ready.
你在跟誰說話？
Who are you talking to?
沒有人
No one.
嗯
Hmm.
這不是真的
That's not true.
我在跟丹說話
I was talking to Dan.
我們繼續保持聯繫的
We go on after.
我們會繼續的
We go on.
他沒事
And he's Okay.
爸爸也是
So is Daddy.
他是真的
He really is.
好的
Good.
你來吧  甜心？
You coming, sweetheart?
等我一分鐘
In a minute.
♪午夜的星星和你在一起♪
"Midnight with the stars And you"
♪午夜和約會♪
"Midnight and a rendezvous"
♪你的眼睛裏藏著一個溫柔的信息♪
"Your eyes Held a message tender"
♪說「我把我所有的愛都交給你」♪
"Saying "I surrender All my love to you"?
♪午夜給我們帶來了甜蜜的浪漫♪
"Midnight brought us Sweet romance"
♪我知道我一生都在做什麼♪
"I know All my whole life through"
♪我會記得你的♪
"I'll be remembering you"
♪不管我還做什麼♪
"Whatever else I do"
♪午夜的星星和你在一起♪
"Midnight with the stars And you"